<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Brandon Boswell</title><link>https://brandonkboswell.com/</link><description>Recent content from Brandon Boswell's Digital Garden</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://brandonkboswell.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>reMarkable Resources when getting started</title><link>https://brandonkboswell.com/blog/reMarkable-Resources-when-getting-started/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 07:50:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonkboswell.com/blog/reMarkable-Resources-when-getting-started/</guid><description>rM2 Template Making rM2 Template Helper &amp;amp; Custom Screens https://youtu.be/7FHBSLMShVc Whitelines for Remarkable https://github.com/Templarian/Remarkable https://rm.ezb.io/
rM2 Highlights Python Library for pulling Remarkable highlights
Screensharing https://github.com/rien/reStream https://github.com/bordaigorl/rmview
Screen Alignment Issues Example and how to fix magnetization</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2 id="rm2-template-making">rM2 Template Making</h2>
<p>

<a target=“_blank” href="https://www.freeremarkabletools.com/index.asp?ds=ok" rel="noopener">rM2 Template Helper &amp; Custom Screens</a>


<a target=“_blank” href="https://youtu.be/7FHBSLMShVc" rel="noopener">https://youtu.be/7FHBSLMShVc</a>


<a target=“_blank” href="https://github.com/steka/reMarkable_templates" rel="noopener">Whitelines for Remarkable</a>


<a target=“_blank” href="https://github.com/Templarian/Remarkable" rel="noopener">https://github.com/Templarian/Remarkable</a>


<a target=“_blank” href="https://rm.ezb.io/" rel="noopener">https://rm.ezb.io/</a></p>
<h2 id="rm2-highlights">rM2 Highlights</h2>
<p>

<a target=“_blank” href="https://remarking.readthedocs.io/en/latest/usage.html" rel="noopener">Python Library for pulling Remarkable highlights</a></p>
<h2 id="screensharing">Screensharing</h2>
<p>

<a target=“_blank” href="https://github.com/rien/reStream" rel="noopener">https://github.com/rien/reStream</a>


<a target=“_blank” href="https://github.com/bordaigorl/rmview" rel="noopener">https://github.com/bordaigorl/rmview</a></p>
<h2 id="screen-alignment-issues">Screen Alignment Issues</h2>
<p>

<a target=“_blank” href="https://www.reddit.com/r/RemarkableTablet/comments/m82oes/do_you_experience_the_same_weird_bug/?utm_source=share&amp;utm_medium=ios_app&amp;utm_name=iossmf" rel="noopener">Example and how to fix magnetization</a></p>
<h2 id="remarkable-hacking">Remarkable Hacking</h2>
<p>

<a target=“_blank” href="https://github.com/ddvk/remarkable-hacks" rel="noopener">DDVK Hack</a></p>
<ul>
<li>

<a target=“_blank” href="https://github.com/ddvk/remarkable-stylus" rel="noopener">Stylus Hack for use with DDVK</a>


<a target=“_blank” href="https://github.com/isaacwisdom/RemarkableLamyEraser" rel="noopener">Standalone Stylus Hack</a>


<a target=“_blank” href="https://github.com/funkey/recept/" rel="noopener">GitHub - funkey/recept: Pen event interception for line smoothing on the reMarkable 2 tablet</a>


<a target=“_blank” href="https://www.reddit.com/r/RemarkableTablet/comments/78u90n/passwordless_ssh_setup_for_remarkable_tablet/" rel="noopener">https://www.reddit.com/r/RemarkableTablet/comments/78u90n/passwordless_ssh_setup_for_remarkable_tablet/</a> (Optional, but helpful)


<a target=“_blank” href="http://www.davisr.me/projects/rcu/" rel="noopener">http://www.davisr.me/projects/rcu/</a></li>
</ul>
<h2 id="meta">Meta</h2>
<p>





<a
  href="/reMarkable-2/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/reMarkable-2/">reMarkable 2</a></p>
]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Flow State High and Tips For Achieving it</title><link>https://brandonkboswell.com/blog/Flow-State-High-and-Tips-For-Achieving-it/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 May 2022 08:45:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonkboswell.com/blog/Flow-State-High-and-Tips-For-Achieving-it/</guid><description>There is something satisfying about getting into flow state. As a creative (or anyone who likes to solve tough problems), flow state is where you make progress. I sometimes call this Progress Time.</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There is something satisfying about getting into flow state. As a creative (or anyone who likes to solve tough problems), <em>flow state</em> is where you make progress. I sometimes call this <em>Progress Time</em>. Everything else you do is to keep the lights on, and to improve the chances that you find yourself in flow state.</p>
<h2 id="factors-effecting-flow-state">Factors effecting flow state:</h2>
<ul>
<li>getting good sleep the night before</li>
<li>have my to-dos for the day in order so that they aren&rsquo;t nagging at me</li>
<li>know that I have a block of time allotted where I&rsquo;m not going to accidentally miss my next meeting</li>
<li>Coffee (not too much)</li>
<li>Noise cancelling headphones (even if nothing is playing), there is something about separating myself from my surroundings that is especially helpful.
<ul>
<li>The 





<a
  href="/AirPods-Pro/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/AirPods-Pro/">AirPods Pro</a> are amazing for this because they are lightweight, non-fatiguing and have no cable to get wrapped up in.</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="my-setup">My Setup</h2>
<p>For me, the most reliable way to achieve <em>flow state</em> is to throw in the 

<a target=“_blank” href="https://amzn.to/3yJY1HU" rel="noopener">AirPods Pro</a> headphones and set them to <em>Noise Cancellation</em> and turn on one of the following:</p>
<ul>
<li>

<a target=“_blank” href="https://open.spotify.com/playlist/3Vy94FDF0S5A4FTvKnTWtL?si=279657fa9f034359" rel="noopener">Journaling (No Lyrics) on Spotify</a></li>
<li>

<a target=“_blank” href="https://open.spotify.com/playlist/37i9dQZF1DX1s9knjP51Oa?si=bdbae497376f4858" rel="noopener">Calm Vibes on Spotify</a></li>
<li>

<a target=“_blank” href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=V2VmcuOEqEg" rel="noopener">SKRILLEX LIVE @ ULTRA MUSIC FESTIVAL 2015</a></li>
</ul>
<p>I have much higher quality headphones than the Airpods, but some combination of the noise cancellation, weightlessness, and the lack of a cable makes a huge difference in helping me focus on what I need to get done. I do find it odd that I can either listen to calm, quiet music or aggressive dubstep and they both enable the same thing, but they do. I find listening to unfamiliar music with forward lyrics difficult for <em>concentration</em>. The noise cancellation is also helpful because I find the constant fan noise of the 





<a
  href="/Touchbar-Macbook-Pro/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/Touchbar-Macbook-Pro/">Touchbar Macbook Pro</a> especially annoying.</p>
<p>For listening to music for enjoyment, I prefer the 

<a target=“_blank” href="https://amzn.to/3P22hYr" rel="noopener">Hifiman Sundara</a> headphones.
<em>Use music without lyrics to help achieve flow state</em></p>
]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Weekly Reflection</title><link>https://brandonkboswell.com/blog/Weekly-Reflection/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 13:16:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonkboswell.com/blog/Weekly-Reflection/</guid><description>Why do weekly reflection? The progress you are making in your life can sometimes be difficult to see in realtime, but is fairly easy see after the fact if you go look for it.</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2 id="why-do-weekly-reflection">Why do weekly reflection?</h2>
<ul>
<li>The progress you are making in your life can sometimes be difficult to see in realtime, but is fairly easy see after the fact if you go look for it. By spending 5 minutes each evening writing about your day you can learn so much about yourself and it&rsquo;s rewarding to look back and see the all the good things that happen in life and your progress.</li>
<li>I&rsquo;m constantly amazed how easy it is to forget the great things that happen in life if you don&rsquo;t take a moment to write them down. Often when I sit down for weekly review I will be reminded of great things that I had already forgotten about. Weekly and annual review allow us to keep these things and continue to enjoy them.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="how-to-get-started-with-basic-intention-setting">How to get started with basic intention setting</h2>
<ul>
<li>3 things you&rsquo;re grateful for.</li>
<li>Pick one daily highlight to focus on for today. 1 simple thing that if you did today, then today would be a success.</li>
<li>Have a spot for notes
<ul>
<li>Capture those as the day goes along</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>End the day with &ldquo;Today was a good day because&hellip;&rdquo;</li>
<li>If you haven&rsquo;t tried it out then check out One Thing, it&rsquo;s this great little app that lets you keep your daily highlight front and center so you can&rsquo;t forget it.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="choose-a-day-that-you-startend-your-week-on-and-do-weekly-reflection">Choose a day that you start/end your week on and do weekly reflection.</h2>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Catalog the week&rsquo;s:</p>
<ul>
<li>Accomplishments</li>
<li>Highs</li>
<li>Lows</li>
<li>Learnings</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<p>Anything you would like to improve.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Start a document for next week and set 1-2 intentions for the week. Things that you think you can/should do over the next week. They don&rsquo;t have to be big, just something that will have progressed you forward in some small way.</p>
<ul>
<li>For me, it&rsquo;s commonly making sure I release a video, or share a past video for those who may have missed it. Which reminds me if you&rsquo;re enjoying the video please like and subscribe and if you&rsquo;re already a subscriber, please share this video with someone who could benefit from it.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<p>Are your daily highlights fit into the bigger picture of your weekly and life goals?</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><strong>Simple Checklist</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Review Obsidian Notes from the Last Week</li>
<li>Review iPad Notes from the Last Week</li>
<li>Clear out anything in the Drafts Inbox </li>
<li>Did you complete what you set out to do?</li>
<li>Reflect on what was accomplished this past week</li>
<li>Plan out the upcoming week</li>
<li>Organize / Prioritize the Inbox</li>
<li>Review the Backlog</li>
<li>Does your calendar match your priorities and values?</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="pro-tips-for-this">Pro Tips for this</h2>
<ul>
<li>Use the Calendar and Temporal Notes plugin if you&rsquo;re not already doing so.</li>
<li>Set a keyboard shortcut to go to today&rsquo;s daily note</li>
<li>Set a keyboard shortcut to go back a day and forward a day so that you don&rsquo;t have to leave focus mode if you don&rsquo;t want to.</li>
<li>Keep your weekly note somewhere visible so that you don&rsquo;t miss out on your weekly intentions just because they were out of sight-out-of-mind.</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Why I don't use VIM</title><link>https://brandonkboswell.com/blog/Why-I-dont-use-VIM/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2022 22:43:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonkboswell.com/blog/Why-I-dont-use-VIM/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m fairly confident that I&amp;rsquo;m going to get a bunch of hateful comments from this article, but please hear me out. I really like the idea of VIM. The ability to move around the page completely with your keyboard is right up my alley.</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I&rsquo;m fairly confident that I&rsquo;m going to get a bunch of hateful comments from this article, but please hear me out. I really like the idea of VIM. The ability to move around the page completely with your keyboard is right up my alley. So much so that I use 





<a
  href="/Vimium/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/Vimium/">Vimium</a> within Chrome. The ability to find and jump to any element on the page or click on any button with a few keystrokes is amazing. If you&rsquo;re interested in that, I have a video all about 





<a
  href="/Vimium/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/Vimium/">Vimium</a>. The issue is that every app you use has to support VIM movements to make the payoff worthwhile. There are tools like <em>kindaVim</em> that try to bring a VIM experience to MacOS, but it still doesn&rsquo;t feel fully baked. We&rsquo;re most of the way there, but you can&rsquo;t use VIM commands in URL fields or to navigate within Electron apps and it&rsquo;s just too painful to have these superpowers and to only be able to use them 80% of the time. Not to mention, I worry a bit about betting my entire ability to work my computer on one app that intends to be paid. It seems like a great way to get held ransom in the future.</p>
<p>I&rsquo;m sure at this point you&rsquo;re like &ldquo;Brandon, if you&rsquo;re so against VIM what are you going to use instead?&rdquo; I&rsquo;m going to use my keyboard, just remapped a bit. The key thing I find myself hating about my current keyboard setup that I have tried to fix with VIM is rapid navigation and selection. I feel like I&rsquo;ve gotten most of the way there by borrowing a handful of navigation commands from <em>Jason Rudolph</em>&rsquo;s 

<a target=“_blank” href="https://github.com/jasonrudolph/keyboard" rel="noopener">Keyboard</a>
which I call 





<a
  href="/Super-Duper-Keyboard/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/Super-Duper-Keyboard/">Super Duper Keyboard</a>. It allows me to get Command, Option, Shift and all the arrow keys without having to leave the home row. Yes, this isn&rsquo;t all the power of VIM, but it gets me the parts that I feel I use constantly and I&rsquo;m confident that they work everywhere because it just uses native MacOS cursor navigation just with the convenience of being on the home row.</p>
<p>Full disclosure, as of the time of this writing: I have only been using this for about two weeks, so it&rsquo;s not fully in muscle memory yet, but it feels surprisingly natural.</p>
<h2 id="key-features">Key Features:</h2>
<ul>
<li>Cursor Movement without leaving the home row</li>
<li>Move a Word forward and back</li>
<li>Move to end of line, beginning of line</li>
<li>Selection with each of them</li>
<li>Lastly, delete a word forward or back (I currently have it on the default of alt+h and alt+l, but I&rsquo;m considering moving those to hyper+h and hyper+l)</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Mentioned in this article:</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>





<a
  href="/VIM/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/VIM/">VIM</a></li>
<li>





<a
  href="/Vimium/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/Vimium/">Vimium</a></li>
<li><em>kindaVim</em> — 

<a target=“_blank” href="https://kindavim.app/" rel="noopener">Link</a></li>
<li>Jason Rudolph&rsquo;s 





<a
  href="/Super-Duper-Keyboard/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/Super-Duper-Keyboard/">Super Duper Keyboard</a></li>
<li>





<a
  href="/Karabiner/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/Karabiner/">Karabiner</a></li>
<li>





<a
  href="/Hammerspoon/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/Hammerspoon/">Hammerspoon</a></li>
</ul>
<h3 id="if-you-are-a-vim-user-i-would-love-to-know-what-is-the-feature-that-makes-it-worth-it-feel-free-to-use-the-link-below-to-email-me">If you are a VIM user, I would love to know what is the feature that makes it worth it, feel free to use the link below to email me.</h3>
]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>My Favorite Gear</title><link>https://brandonkboswell.com/blog/My-Favorite-Gear/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2022 10:59:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonkboswell.com/blog/My-Favorite-Gear/</guid><description>Desk Boox Note Air 2 Plus — My favorite eInk tablet and has replaced traditional pen and paper for me. Samsung S-Pen S6 Lite — My preferred stylus for use at my desk LAMY AL-Star Black EMR with POM Tip — My preferred stylus on the go due to the cap.</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2 id="desk">Desk</h2>
<ul>
<li>

<a target=“_blank” href="https://amzn.to/3cn9JiU" rel="noopener">Boox Note Air 2 Plus</a> — My favorite eInk tablet and has replaced traditional pen and paper for me.
<ul>
<li>

<a target=“_blank” href="https://amzn.to/3BcdPVx" rel="noopener">Samsung S-Pen S6 Lite</a> — My preferred stylus for use at my desk</li>
<li>

<a target=“_blank” href="https://amzn.to/3IMXCrA" rel="noopener">LAMY AL-Star Black EMR with POM Tip</a> — My preferred stylus on the go due to the cap.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>

<a target=“_blank” href="https://amzn.to/3P5T4hE" rel="noopener">Kindle Oasis</a> — If you&rsquo;re buying today, buy the 

<a target=“_blank” href="https://amzn.to/3bPw1cG" rel="noopener">Paperwhite</a> instead. My thoughts on 





<a
  href="/Kindle/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/Kindle/">Kindle</a>.</li>
<li>

<a target=“_blank” href="https://amzn.to/3OZygsa" rel="noopener">Endgame Gear XM1</a> — I have a 

<a target=“_blank” href="https://www.endgamegear.com/xm2w/gaming-mice" rel="noopener">wireless XM2w</a> on order, but this mouse fits me better than all others, and I have tried a ton.</li>
<li>





<a
  href="/Fully-Jarvis-Desk/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/Fully-Jarvis-Desk/">Fully Jarvis Desk</a> — A little shakey, but ultimately excellent price to performance.</li>
<li>





<a
  
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link broken"
  data-src="../Herman%20Miller%20Embody">Herman Miller Embody</a> — Still new to this one, but it&rsquo;s a major upgrade over the 

<a target=“_blank” href="https://secretlab.co/collections/omega-series" rel="noopener">Secret Labs Omega</a> I used before. The Omega was a great chair, but didn&rsquo;t fit me well. Secret Labs has amazing support, so if the chair fits you well, go for it.</li>
<li>

<a target=“_blank” href="https://drop.com/buy/drop-signature-series-space-race-keyboard" rel="noopener">Drop Alt Signature Series Space Race</a> — Similar to the Studio Neat Mark One above, a bit expensive, but makes me want to type. The stock stabilizers are trash, but after fixing that it&rsquo;s a great keyboard</li>
<li>

<a target=“_blank” href="https://amzn.to/3bNHOZ1" rel="noopener">Sony DualSense Wireless Controller</a> — 1000 hertz. Doesn&rsquo;t fit quite as good in the hand as the DS4, but is of amazing quality.</li>
<li>

<a target=“_blank” href="https://amzn.to/3yftu2Z" rel="noopener">iPad Pro 11in</a> — The easiest way to get the benefits of 





<a
  href="/Analog-Tools/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/Analog-Tools/">Analog Tools</a> while still having the benefits of 





<a
  href="/moc/Digital-Workflow/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/moc/Digital-Workflow/">Digital Workflow</a></li>
</ul>
<h2 id="audio--video">Audio / Video</h2>
<ul>
<li>

<a target=“_blank” href="https://amzn.to/3P22hYr" rel="noopener">Hifiman Sundara</a> (For Music)</li>
<li>

<a target=“_blank” href="https://amzn.to/3yG3SxE" rel="noopener">Schiit Modi</a> — No frills, but works and sounds great</li>
<li>

<a target=“_blank” href="https://amzn.to/3IjobV4" rel="noopener">Schiit Magni Heresy</a> (AVOID)— Had two break and Schiit&rsquo;s repair policy is awful</li>
<li>

<a target=“_blank” href="https://jdslabs.com/product/atom-amp/" rel="noopener">JDS Labs Atom Amp+</a> — Sounds as good as the Schiit, but doesn&rsquo;t break. The case isn&rsquo;t as nice as the heresy, but after swapping out 

<a target=“_blank” href="https://jdslabs.com/product/black-aluminum-knob-taiss/" rel="noopener">the knob</a> it is just as nice.</li>
<li>

<a target=“_blank” href="https://amzn.to/3yJY1HU" rel="noopener">AirPods Pro</a> (For Focus)</li>
<li>

<a target=“_blank” href="https://amzn.to/3yFQolI" rel="noopener">Sonos One</a> — So easy and great sounding</li>
<li>

<a target=“_blank” href="https://amzn.to/3IcLDDj" rel="noopener">Sonos Five</a> — Expensive, but excellent sound</li>
<li>

<a target=“_blank” href="https://amzn.to/3R7T3vA" rel="noopener">Sony ZV-E10</a>
<ul>
<li>

<a target=“_blank” href="https://amzn.to/3NIa0tB" rel="noopener">Sigma 16mm f1.4</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>

<a target=“_blank” href="https://amzn.to/3agyCfn" rel="noopener">Samson Q2U</a> — Great sounding, but inexpensive microphone.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="analog-tools">Analog Tools</h2>
<ul>
<li>

<a target=“_blank” href="https://baronfig.com/tools/confidant/classic?size=flagship&#43;%285.4%22&#43;x&#43;7.7%22%29&amp;color=charcoal&amp;paper&#43;type=dot&#43;grid" rel="noopener">Baron Fig Confidant</a> — IMHO it takes ink better than the Moleskine</li>
<li>

<a target=“_blank” href="https://www.studioneat.com/products/markone" rel="noopener">Studio Neat Mark One</a> — An expensive pen, but feels great in the hand and it makes me want to write more</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="other">Other</h2>
<ul>
<li>

<a target=“_blank” href="https://amzn.to/3bSAV8H" rel="noopener">Delonghi Magnifica</a> — Expensive, but excellent coffee</li>
<li>

<a target=“_blank” href="https://smartish.com/collections/wallet-cases/products/smartish-wallet-slayer-vol-2-card-case-for-iphone-x-xs-silk" rel="noopener">Silk Wallet Case</a> — All in One Case+Wallet for iPhone, but not good for inductive charging</li>
<li>The 

<a target=“_blank” href="https://www.awaytravel.com/travel-bags/front-pocket-backpack?color=navy_nylon" rel="noopener">Away Front Pocket Backpack</a> — My Incase backpack of 10 years recently separated at the zipper and I needed to buy a new pack and picked up this one. I also tried the 

<a target=“_blank” href="https://www.awaytravel.com/travel-bags/everywhere-zip-backpack?color=navy_nylon" rel="noopener">Away Everywhere Zip Backpack</a>, but didn&rsquo;t like that bag nearly as much.</li>
<li>

<a target=“_blank” href="https://www.tesla.com/model3" rel="noopener">Tesla Model 3</a> — I tested all of the other electric cars in 2021 and ended up coming back to the Model 3. As of the time of this writing, Tesla is very far ahead of the other players in electric cars. This will likely change over the next 2-3 years</li>
<li>

<a target=“_blank” href="https://byloftie.com/products/loftie" rel="noopener">Loftie</a> — A great alarm clock that keeps me away from my phone in the morning, and discourages snoozing. Has way more features than I need, but is an excellent alarm clock that is a joy to use.</li>
</ul>
<p><em>This post contains affiliate links. If you use these links to buy something, I may earn a commission. Thank you for supporting the blog.</em></p>
]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Publishing your Obsidian Vault Online with Quartz</title><link>https://brandonkboswell.com/blog/Publishing-your-Obsidian-Vault-Online-with-Quartz/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonkboswell.com/blog/Publishing-your-Obsidian-Vault-Online-with-Quartz/</guid><description>So you&amp;rsquo;re thinking about publishing your Obsidian Vault online, but you&amp;rsquo;re not sure if you want to pay for Obsidian Publish or not. I&amp;rsquo;ve been there, that was the exact same situation I was in when I considered publishing my vault. Call me cheap, but I wasn&amp;rsquo;t sure if I was ready to pay $20 a month for the rest of time. Would I keep writing meaningful content, would people actually ready it? So instead, I decided I was going to figure out a way to publish my vault without the monthly fee. I now publish my vault online, and I don&amp;rsquo;t pay anything for hosting.</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<blockquote>
<p>NOTE: The easiest way to publish your vault online is by using 

<a target=“_blank” href="https://obsidian.md/publish" rel="noopener">Obsidian Publish</a>. I put a bunch of time into figuring out how all of this would work together, and I probably could have saved a bunch of time by just using Obsidian Publish. Either way, I&rsquo;ve learned a ton in setting this up. I also have more control on what does and doesn&rsquo;t get published. I have a ton of private content in my vault and I do not want that being published, which is why I went to all this trouble you&rsquo;re about to see. Yes, I could use multiple vaults, but that seems annoying when you want to link to something that resides in another vault.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>So you&rsquo;re thinking about publishing your 





<a
  href="/Obsidian/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/Obsidian/">Obsidian</a> Vault online, but you&rsquo;re not sure if you want to pay for <em>Obsidian Publish</em> or not. I&rsquo;ve been there, that was the exact same situation I was in when I considered publishing my vault. Call me cheap, but I wasn&rsquo;t sure if I was ready to pay $20 a month for the rest of time. Would I keep writing meaningful content, would people actually ready it? So instead, I decided I was going to figure out a way to publish my vault without the monthly fee. I now publish my vault online, and I don&rsquo;t pay anything for hosting. <strong>(You are currently reading this article from the digital vault that I publish through this method)</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>For me, I cobbled together a combination of:
<ul>
<li>

<a target=“_blank” href="https://github.com/jackyzha0/quartz" rel="noopener"><strong>Quartz</strong></a>
<ul>
<li>A nice, clean-looking template for your digital garden that sits on top of <em>Hugo</em>. Once you get your bearings with it, you will find that it is just a <em>Hugo</em> site and you can customize it a ton if you would like.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><strong>

<a target=“_blank” href="https://github.com/brandonkboswell/obsidian-export/tree/title_frontmatter" rel="noopener">Obsidian Export</a></strong> (Slightly Modified)
<ul>
<li>A Rust based library for converting your Obsidian Vault to standards compliant <em>Markdown</em> that supports translating Obsidian style links to standard links that are compatible with Hugo.</li>
<li>Quartz and Hugo both assume that all of your files have a title attribute in their frontmatter. Unfortunately, most of my files do not have this title front matter. I have a branch of obsidian-export (linked above) that uses the file&rsquo;s name to generate titles when that frontmatter is not present.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><strong>

<a target=“_blank” href="https://github.com/jackyzha0/hugo-obsidian" rel="noopener">obsidian-hugo</a></strong>
<ul>
<li><em>Quartz</em> has an easy setup that allows you to commit all of your content to <em>Github</em> and it will compile everything via <em>Github Actions</em>. This is fantastic and super helpful. The issue is I have private content that I don&rsquo;t want on Github.</li>
<li>So instead I use the <em>obsidian-hugo</em> library that Quartz&rsquo;s Github Action uses just I use it on my local machine and precompile the filtered content before uploading to Github. This enables me to host my Digital Garden on Github (for free) without risking private content accidentally leaking out onto the internet.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>

<a target=“_blank” href="https://docs.github.com/en/pages/quickstart" rel="noopener"><strong>Github Pages</strong></a>
<ul>
<li>This is where I publish the content that gets output. It&rsquo;s all static html and is being served by Github. There is no amount of traffic I could ever manage to generate that Github couldn&rsquo;t handle.</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="why-do-i-use-obsidian-export-when-obsidian-hugo-is-required-by-quartz-and-does-most-of-the-same-things">Why do I use Obsidian Export when Obsidian Hugo is required by Quartz and does most of the same things?</h3>
<ul>
<li><strong>obsidian-export</strong> does a very good job of filtering out files and folders you don&rsquo;t want exported</li>
<li>it makes me confident that there is no chance that private data gets uploaded by not even allowing that data to be in the folder that gets parsed</li>
<li>It handles bad or no frontmatter so that the downstream pipeline doesn&rsquo;t have any issues</li>
<li>You can avoid a bunch of hacks to Quartz (and your layout files) by ensuring that your files have title attributes in their frontmatter. I have hacked together a fork of obsidian-export that does this automatically based on the file name when exporting. 

<a target=“_blank” href="https://github.com/brandonkboswell/obsidian-export/tree/title_frontmatter" rel="noopener">https://github.com/brandonkboswell/obsidian-export/tree/title_frontmatter</a></li>
</ul>
<h1 id="high-level-steps-these-are-from-memory-as-i-set-this-up-a-few-months-ago">High Level Steps (these are from memory as I set this up a few months ago)</h1>
<ol>
<li>Clone 

<a target=“_blank” href="https://github.com/jackyzha0/quartz" rel="noopener">Quartz</a> into a local directory</li>
<li>Create a Repo on Github to host your public garden
<ol>
<li>

<a target=“_blank” href="https://levelup.gitconnected.com/build-a-personal-website-with-github-pages-and-hugo-6c68592204c7" rel="noopener">Getting started with Github Pages</a></li>
<li>

<a target=“_blank” href="https://docs.github.com/en/pages/configuring-a-custom-domain-for-your-github-pages-site" rel="noopener">Configuring a Custom Domain for your Github Pages Site</a></li>
</ol>
</li>
<li>Make the public folder of your Quartz repo a submodule of that repo
<ol>
<li><code>git submodule add &lt;your_github_project_url&gt; ./public</code></li>
</ol>
</li>
<li>Install Hugo for minifying and running a local server
<ol>
<li><code>brew install hugo</code></li>
</ol>
</li>
<li>Clone obsidian-export wherever you keep libraries
<ol>
<li>Obsidian Export runs in <em>Rust</em>, so make sure you have Rust enabled on your machine</li>
<li>If I remember correctly, I ran <code>cargo build</code> from the obsidian-export directory to build a local binary that can be called in the compile script</li>
</ol>
</li>
<li>Clone obsidian-hugo wherever you keep libraries
<ol>
<li>Obsidian-hugo runs in <em>Go</em>, so make sure you have Go enabled on your machine and in your PATH;</li>
<li>The watch/compile script will run <code>go run ~/Sites/hugo-obsidian -input=/Users/brandonkboswell/Sites/quartz/content -output=/Users/brandonkboswell/Sites/quartz/assets/indices -index -root=/Users/brandonkboswell/Sites/quartz;</code> when it compiles.</li>
</ol>
</li>
<li>Update the compile and watch scripts for the paths of your folders
<ol>
<li>My quartz directory is at: ~/Sites/quartz</li>
<li>My Obsidian Vault is at (My <em>iCloud</em> Folder): ~/Library/Mobile\ Documents/iCloud~md~obsidian/Documents/bkb</li>
<li>My hugo-obsidian directory is at: ~/Sites/hugo-obsidian</li>
</ol>
</li>
<li>Configure your configuration files
<ol>
<li><strong>Hugo Config</strong> — quartz/config.toml file</li>
<li><strong>Quartz Config</strong> — data/config.yaml</li>
<li><strong>Quartz Graph Config</strong> — data/graphConfig.yaml</li>
</ol>
</li>
<li>Add a file name <strong>.export-ignore</strong> to your Obsidian Vault
<ol>
<li>Obsidian Export will skip any files / folders you mention here and make sure they don&rsquo;t get handed to Quartz</li>
<li>You can&rsquo;t create this file in Obsidian (you likely want to use the finder or a Code Editor).</li>
<li>A sample of my .export-ignore file is further down in this article</li>
</ol>
</li>
<li>Run the watch script (which will do an initial compile and then watch for changes to your Obsidian Vault)
<ol>
<li>Note that the compile script empties out your quartz/content directory so that files that may have been moved or deleted from your Obsidian Vault do not end up being pushed to the public internet. <strong>Make sure that this path is set correctly before running the watch or compile script.</strong></li>
</ol>
</li>
<li>Start a hugo server from your quartz directory
<ol>
<li><code>./serve.sh</code></li>
</ol>
</li>
<li>Assuming everything worked, you should be able to preview your vault at: localhost:1313</li>
<li>Tinker / tweak for way too long</li>
<li>When you&rsquo;re ready you can commit your quartz/public directory to Github pages
<ol>
<li><strong>Verify <em>(especially for the first commit)</em> that there is nothing private that you don&rsquo;t want uploaded to the internet.</strong></li>
<li><code>cd ~/Sites/quartz/public; git add .; git commit -m &quot;Update&quot;; git push origin</code></li>
</ol>
</li>
</ol>
<hr>
<h2 id="configure-your-export-ignore-file-at-the-root-of-your-obsidian-vault-heres-mine">Configure your .export-ignore file at the root of your Obsidian Vault. Here&rsquo;s mine:</h2>
<div class="highlight"><div class="chroma">
<table class="lntable"><tr><td class="lntd">
<pre tabindex="0" class="chroma"><code><span class="lnt"> 1
</span><span class="lnt"> 2
</span><span class="lnt"> 3
</span><span class="lnt"> 4
</span><span class="lnt"> 5
</span><span class="lnt"> 6
</span><span class="lnt"> 7
</span><span class="lnt"> 8
</span><span class="lnt"> 9
</span><span class="lnt">10
</span><span class="lnt">11
</span><span class="lnt">12
</span><span class="lnt">13
</span><span class="lnt">14
</span><span class="lnt">15
</span></code></pre></td>
<td class="lntd">
<pre tabindex="0" class="chroma"><code class="language-fallback" data-lang="fallback">templates/*
private/*
1-1/*
business/*
collections/*
people/*
to_publish/*
files/*
temporal/*
personal/*
screenshots/*
ideas/*
.trash/*
.obsidian/*
_content_calendar.md
</code></pre></td></tr></table>
</div>
</div><h2 id="to-compile-your-notes-once">To compile your notes once</h2>
<div class="highlight"><div class="chroma">
<table class="lntable"><tr><td class="lntd">
<pre tabindex="0" class="chroma"><code><span class="lnt"> 1
</span><span class="lnt"> 2
</span><span class="lnt"> 3
</span><span class="lnt"> 4
</span><span class="lnt"> 5
</span><span class="lnt"> 6
</span><span class="lnt"> 7
</span><span class="lnt"> 8
</span><span class="lnt"> 9
</span><span class="lnt">10
</span></code></pre></td>
<td class="lntd">
<pre tabindex="0" class="chroma"><code class="language-bash" data-lang="bash"><span class="cp">#!/bin/bash
</span><span class="cp"></span>
<span class="nb">cd</span> ~/Sites/quartz<span class="p">;</span> ./compile.sh

--- compile.sh ---

<span class="c1">#!/bin/bash</span>

<span class="nb">cd</span> ~/Sites/hugo-obsidian<span class="p">;</span> rm -fr ~/Sites/quartz/content/*<span class="p">;</span> rm -rf ~/Sites/quartz/public/*<span class="p">;</span> ~/Sites/obsidian-export/target/debug/obsidian-export --add-titles --frontmatter<span class="o">=</span>always ~/Library/Mobile<span class="se">\ </span>Documents/iCloud~md~obsidian/Documents/bkb ~/Sites/quartz/content<span class="p">;</span> go run ~/Sites/hugo-obsidian -input<span class="o">=</span>/Users/brandonkboswell/Sites/quartz/content -output<span class="o">=</span>/Users/brandonkboswell/Sites/quartz/assets/indices -index -root<span class="o">=</span>/Users/brandonkboswell/Sites/quartz<span class="p">;</span> <span class="o">(</span><span class="nb">cd</span> ~/Sites/quartz <span class="o">&amp;&amp;</span> hugo --minify<span class="o">)</span>

</code></pre></td></tr></table>
</div>
</div><h2 id="to-recompile-your-notes-on-change">To recompile your notes on change</h2>
<div class="highlight"><div class="chroma">
<table class="lntable"><tr><td class="lntd">
<pre tabindex="0" class="chroma"><code><span class="lnt">1
</span><span class="lnt">2
</span><span class="lnt">3
</span><span class="lnt">4
</span><span class="lnt">5
</span><span class="lnt">6
</span><span class="lnt">7
</span><span class="lnt">8
</span></code></pre></td>
<td class="lntd">
<pre tabindex="0" class="chroma"><code class="language-bash" data-lang="bash"><span class="nb">cd</span> ~/Sites/quartz<span class="p">;</span> ./watch.sh

--- watch.sh ---

<span class="c1">#!/bin/bash</span>

<span class="nb">export</span> <span class="nv">GOPATH</span><span class="o">=</span>/Users/<span class="nv">$USER</span>/go<span class="p">;</span> <span class="nb">export</span> <span class="nv">GOROOT</span><span class="o">=</span><span class="s2">&#34;</span><span class="k">$(</span>/usr/local/bin/brew --prefix golang<span class="k">)</span><span class="s2">/libexec&#34;</span><span class="p">;</span> <span class="nb">export</span> <span class="nv">PATH</span><span class="o">=</span><span class="s2">&#34;</span><span class="nv">$PATH</span><span class="s2">:</span><span class="si">${</span><span class="nv">GOPATH</span><span class="si">}</span><span class="s2">/bin:</span><span class="si">${</span><span class="nv">GOROOT</span><span class="si">}</span><span class="s2">/bin&#34;</span><span class="p">;</span> <span class="nb">cd</span> ~/Sites/quartz<span class="p">;</span> nodemon -w ~/Library/Mobile<span class="se">\ </span>Documents/iCloud~md~obsidian/Documents/bkb -w ~/Sites/quartz/assets/js -w ~/Sites/quartz/assets/styles -w ~/Sites/quartz/layouts -w ~/Sites/quartz/config.toml -w ~/Sites/quartz/data/config.yaml -x <span class="s2">&#34;~/Sites/quartz/compile.sh&#34;</span> -e md,html,js,scss,xml

</code></pre></td></tr></table>
</div>
</div><h2 id="to-preview-your-changes-before-pushing-to-github-you-can-run-a-local-hugo-server">To preview your changes before pushing to Github, you can run a local hugo server:</h2>
<p>Sometimes the server will crash while the compile script is rebuilding everything. If you wrap the hugo server code in a while loop then it will restart itself if this happens. For this I will have two terminal panes open on for the watch script and one for the hugo server. As I make changes to my Obsidian Vault or the Quartz files it will recompile the content and then hugo will recompile, at which point you can refresh your browser to see the change. Usually that will be at localhost:1313.</p>
<div class="highlight"><div class="chroma">
<table class="lntable"><tr><td class="lntd">
<pre tabindex="0" class="chroma"><code><span class="lnt">1
</span><span class="lnt">2
</span><span class="lnt">3
</span></code></pre></td>
<td class="lntd">
<pre tabindex="0" class="chroma"><code class="language-bash" data-lang="bash"><span class="o">(</span><span class="k">while</span> true<span class="p">;</span> <span class="k">do</span> 
	hugo server --disableFastRender
<span class="k">done</span><span class="o">)</span> <span class="p">&amp;</span>
</code></pre></td></tr></table>
</div>
</div><h2 id="when-im-ready-to-publish-an-update-to-github">When I&rsquo;m ready to publish an update to Github:</h2>
<p>Go to the garden folder and commit those changes:</p>
<div class="highlight"><div class="chroma">
<table class="lntable"><tr><td class="lntd">
<pre tabindex="0" class="chroma"><code><span class="lnt">1
</span></code></pre></td>
<td class="lntd">
<pre tabindex="0" class="chroma"><code class="language-bash" data-lang="bash"><span class="nb">cd</span> ~/sites/quartz/public<span class="p">;</span> git add .<span class="p">;</span> git commit -m <span class="s2">&#34;Update&#34;</span><span class="p">;</span> git push origin
</code></pre></td></tr></table>
</div>
</div><h2 id="additional-notes">Additional Notes</h2>
<ul>
<li>You probably want to do your ignoring of personal files at the obsidian-export level because if a file is referenced in another file, but that file is flagged as a draft in the frontmatter then hugo-obsidian will have trouble with that and make hugo error on compile with the backlinks. Doing your ignoring of specific files in obsidian-export takes care of this.</li>
<li>If you&rsquo;ve never used <em>Hugo</em> before (like I hadn&rsquo;t prior to this project), you may not know that Hugo has a static folder that generates assets you want to be in any subsequent rebuilds. When I first started this project I added a bunch of lines to the compile script to create files and moving files around when all I really needed to do was add those files to my static folder.</li>
<li>You are going to want to update your Hugo layout files to take advantage of the backlink rendering provided by Obsidian Export. The changes you&rsquo;ll want to make, plus an explanation are available here: 

<a target=“_blank” href="https://github.com/zoni/obsidian-export/issues/8#issuecomment-774521792" rel="noopener">https://github.com/zoni/obsidian-export/issues/8#issuecomment-774521792</a></li>
</ul>
<h2 id="previous-attempts">Previous Attempts</h2>
<ul>
<li>Originally I modified hugo-obsidian to get around the no titles issue, since I now do this in obsidian-export I no longer need to maintain a fork of that code. If it&rsquo;s useful to you, here is the change I made:
<ul>
<li>I had to make a minor modification to obsidian-hugo because it assumes that all of your files have a title attribute in their frontmatter. Unfortunately, most of my files do not have this title front matter. I have a branch of obsidian-hugo that uses the file&rsquo;s name to generate titles if that frontmatter is not present. 

<a target=“_blank” href="https://github.com/brandonkboswell/hugo-obsidian/tree/without_titles" rel="noopener">https://github.com/brandonkboswell/hugo-obsidian/tree/without_titles</a>.
<em>As the time of this writing, that branch has not been merged into the main repo, but it may have by the time you&rsquo;re reading this.</em></li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Quicklaunch your commonly used applications with Karabiner Elements</title><link>https://brandonkboswell.com/blog/Quicklaunch-your-commonly-used-applications-with-Karabiner-Elements/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 12:25:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonkboswell.com/blog/Quicklaunch-your-commonly-used-applications-with-Karabiner-Elements/</guid><description>What shortcuts do I use? O Launching Originally found it watching a YouTube Video by Jesse Skelton which you can find here https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uaJSjgVEhMQ M -&amp;gt; Music -&amp;gt; Spotify I -&amp;gt; IM -&amp;gt; Messages F -&amp;gt; Files -&amp;gt; Open Downloads Folder G -&amp;gt; Google Chrome -&amp;gt; Chrome C -&amp;gt; Calendar -&amp;gt; Fantastical T -&amp;gt; TickTick -&amp;gt; TickTick Z -&amp;gt; Zoom -&amp;gt; Zoom D -&amp;gt; Obsidian -&amp;gt; Obsidian E -&amp;gt; Editor -&amp;gt; Sublime Text S -&amp;gt; Slack -&amp;gt; Slack Hyper Key This gives me an extra set of Keyboard Shortcut triggers without having to develop Carpel Tunnel or having to leave my home row.</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2 id="what-shortcuts-do-i-use">What shortcuts do I use?</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>O Launching</strong>
<ul>
<li>Originally found it watching a YouTube Video by <em>Jesse Skelton</em> which you can find here 

<a target=“_blank” href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uaJSjgVEhMQ" rel="noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uaJSjgVEhMQ</a>
<ul>
<li>M -&gt; Music -&gt; Spotify</li>
<li>I -&gt; IM -&gt; Messages</li>
<li>F -&gt; Files -&gt; Open Downloads Folder</li>
<li>G -&gt; Google Chrome -&gt; Chrome</li>
<li>C -&gt; Calendar -&gt; Fantastical</li>
<li>T -&gt; TickTick -&gt; TickTick</li>
<li>Z -&gt; Zoom -&gt; Zoom</li>
<li>D -&gt; Obsi<strong>d</strong>ian -&gt; Obsidian</li>
<li>E -&gt; Editor -&gt; Sublime Text</li>
<li>S -&gt; Slack -&gt; Slack</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><strong>Hyper Key</strong>
<ul>
<li>This gives me an extra set of Keyboard Shortcut triggers without having to develop Carpel Tunnel or having to leave my home row. I used to bind many keyboard shortcuts to CTRL+ALT+COMMAND, but then I would have to leave the home row with the right hand which just leads to typing mistakes when trying to migrate back afterwards. Having the hyper key allows me to do those same shortcuts with my pinky finger on my left hand.
<ul>
<li>CAPS_LOCK to HYPER (SHIFT+COMMAND+OPTION+CONTROL) or ESCAPE (If Alone)</li>
<li>Hyper + i/j/k/l == vim directional Keys</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><strong>HJKL Arrow Keys</strong>
<ul>
<li>Similar to the one above. I used to have one of the old Macbook Pros with the inverted T Arrow keys, and then with the unibody Macbooks with no ports they decided to screw that up. I had a ton of muscle memory for getting to those keys and never could get that back since they changed this. So last year I decided that I was going to move my arrow keys to the home row so I wouldn&rsquo;t have to leave it. This configuration also has Hyper + G for beginning of line and Hyper + ; for end of line, but I honestly never use those.  I just use Hyper+Command+H or L, there&rsquo;s too much muscle memory there that I can&rsquo;t seem to give up.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><strong>Shift+Escape to Tilde</strong>
<ul>
<li>This is largely just a symptom of having a 65% keyboard and needing to type a tilde where there&rsquo;s no key for it. This is what I chose. I have more 65% keyboard hacks in my Keyboard itself that I should probably do a video on. Let me know in the comments if you have any interest in that.</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<p>





<a
  href="/Karabiner/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/Karabiner/">Karabiner</a></p>
]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>How I Use Obsidian</title><link>https://brandonkboswell.com/blog/How-I-Use-Obsidian/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Feb 2022 08:37:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonkboswell.com/blog/How-I-Use-Obsidian/</guid><description>Setting up your Obsidian Vault for Personal Knowledge Management can be daunting. You start from scratch, there are 1000&amp;rsquo;s of plugins to chose from, and honestly it all becomes one big distraction from actually generating thoughts and ideas.</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Setting up your Obsidian Vault for Personal Knowledge Management can be daunting. You start from scratch, there are 1000&rsquo;s of plugins to chose from, and honestly it all becomes one big distraction from actually generating thoughts and ideas. In this video, I will share my approach to managing an Obisidian vault in hopes it will save you a few headaches when starting from scratch.</p>
<p><strong>Note:</strong> I publish my Obsidian Vault using Github Pages and because of this I use more folders than most vaults you will see. Having folders that I can hide away makes making sure I only share what I intend to share with the Internet. If you haven&rsquo;t already go check out my vault at brandonkboswell.com. I will put a link in the description.</p>
<h2 id="folders--major-areas">Folders / Major Areas</h2>
<ul>
<li>1-1
<ul>
<li><em>I thoroughly enjoy writing in Obsidian, so I put my 1-1 notes with people I chat with on a regular basis instead of putting them in another app</em></li>
<li>It&rsquo;s just a running log with a date and the todos associated with that session</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Business
<ul>
<li>A random assortment of notes that I want to keep and link to, but I don&rsquo;t want shared with the world.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Collections
<ul>
<li>Where I collect items I thought were interesting that I want to be able to refer back to, but I might not actually have significant commentary on. Please let me know how you do this in the comments, that way I do this is not ideal. Basically I screenshot or get the URL for whatever it is and then Quick Add to TickTick and then when I clean out my 





<a
  href="/TickTick/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/TickTick/">TickTick</a> Inbox I put it into 





<a
  href="/Obsidian/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/Obsidian/">Obsidian</a> for storage.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Cooking
<ul>
<li>My wife is a far better cook then I, but I do cook a few meals each week. The issue I always found was I would do a meal and then by the time I cook that meal the next time I couldn&rsquo;t remember what I had tried, so I end up making the same mistakes and not progressing at perfecting the dish. So I started creating cooking notes for these and after each time I cook a dish I put another entry into that note. When I go to start cooking that dish again I refer back to what I had written the last time on what to try next.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Ideas
<ul>
<li>A random assortment of ideas. These are mostly a folder just to make them private when publishing</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>People
<ul>
<li>My notes on people. This one is also private as it has a bunch of people who didn&rsquo;t ask to be published online.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Personal
<ul>
<li>Pictures of cards, notes people have sent me or deeply personal writing prompts that don&rsquo;t need to be public</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Projects
<ul>
<li>A folder where all of the Youtube Videos or Articles start while I&rsquo;m figuring them out. Currently this folder is not published, but I might make it public soon and then just apply a draft tag to things that shouldn&rsquo;t be published. For instance the script for this video is in there</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Seedlings
<ul>
<li>This is where all of my <em>Atomic Notes</em> / <em>Evergreen Notes</em> go.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Sources
<ul>
<li>This is where all of my Readwise Highlights &amp; Literary Notes go.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Temporal
<ul>
<li>Daily Notes
<ul>
<li>Ex: 2022-02-25</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Weekly Notes
<ul>
<li>Ex: 2022-W07</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Annual Notes
<ul>
<li>Ex: 





<a
  href="/2021-In-Review/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/2021-In-Review/">2021 In Review</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>To Publish
<ul>
<li>Articles / Documents that would be useful to the public, but need cleanup / refinement before they can be shared</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Underscore Gang — I need to find a way to describe this
<ul>
<li>Index</li>
<li>Content Calendar</li>
<li>Backlogs
<ul>
<li>Gaming Backlog</li>
<li>Idea Backlog</li>
<li>Book Backlog</li>
<li>Music Backlog</li>
<li>TV Backlog</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Seedings</li>
<li>Writing Prompts</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="plugins-i-use">Plugins I use</h2>
<ul>
<li>See Video where I run through this.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="themes">Themes</h2>
<ul>
<li>I use the Minimal Theme</li>
<li>I&rsquo;ve tried the Notational one and the California Coast and they are both good as well, I just happen to like the Minimal Theme slightly more.</li>
</ul>
<p>





<a
  href="/Obsidian/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/Obsidian/">Obsidian</a></p>
]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>My App Essentials</title><link>https://brandonkboswell.com/blog/My-App-Essentials/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 11:04:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonkboswell.com/blog/My-App-Essentials/</guid><description> Obsidian TickTick Skitch HandMirror Amethyst OneThing 1Password Loom GoodNotes Readwise Command MeetingBar Honorable Mentions Drafts Spotify / Tidal iTerm2 Parcel Fantastical</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li>





<a
  href="/Obsidian/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/Obsidian/">Obsidian</a></li>
<li>





<a
  href="/TickTick/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/TickTick/">TickTick</a></li>
<li><em>Skitch</em></li>
<li><em>HandMirror</em></li>
<li>





<a
  href="/Amethyst/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/Amethyst/">Amethyst</a></li>
<li><em>OneThing</em></li>
<li><em>1Password</em></li>
<li>





<a
  href="/Loom/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/Loom/">Loom</a></li>
<li><em>GoodNotes</em></li>
<li>





<a
  href="/Readwise/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/Readwise/">Readwise</a></li>
<li><em>Command</em></li>
<li>





<a
  href="/MeetingBar/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/MeetingBar/">MeetingBar</a></li>
</ul>
<h3 id="honorable-mentions">Honorable Mentions</h3>
<ul>
<li><em>Drafts</em></li>
<li><em>Spotify</em> / <em>Tidal</em></li>
<li>





<a
  href="/iTerm2/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/iTerm2/">iTerm2</a></li>
<li><em>Parcel</em></li>
<li><em>Fantastical</em></li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>My process for keeping in touch with people using TickTick</title><link>https://brandonkboswell.com/blog/My-process-for-keeping-in-touch-with-people-using-TickTick/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 22:53:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonkboswell.com/blog/My-process-for-keeping-in-touch-with-people-using-TickTick/</guid><description/><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title>How I keep my Chrome Tabs under control with "Merge All Windows" Chrome Extension</title><link>https://brandonkboswell.com/blog/How-I-keep-my-Chrome-Tabs-under-control-with-Merge-All-Windows-Chrome-Extension/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 22:47:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonkboswell.com/blog/How-I-keep-my-Chrome-Tabs-under-control-with-Merge-All-Windows-Chrome-Extension/</guid><description/><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title>Vimium is not just for Developers</title><link>https://brandonkboswell.com/blog/Vimium-is-not-just-for-Developers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 21:53:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonkboswell.com/blog/Vimium-is-not-just-for-Developers/</guid><description>Chrome Extensions
This video is by no means an exhaustive list of everything Vimium can do, but I can walk you through the features I use everyday that I think are a good starting point and then you can decide if you want to mix in anything else.</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>





<a
  href="/Chrome-Extensions/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/Chrome-Extensions/">Chrome Extensions</a></p>
<p>This video is by no means an exhaustive list of everything 





<a
  href="/Vimium/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/Vimium/">Vimium</a> can do, but I can walk you through the features I use everyday that I think are a good starting point and then you can decide if you want to mix in anything else.</p>
<h3 id="features-i-actually-use">Features I actually use:</h3>
<ul>
<li>J/K Arrow Keys</li>
<li>F to tap on any button</li>
<li>/ to search for any word on the page and then double tap enter to click on that link
<ul>
<li>If there are multiple instances of the word on the page you can tap enter once to commit the search and then use n to jump to the next instance of it.</li>
<li>Shift N to go back</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<p>Be sure to check out the available commands in the settings. There are bunch of good commands in here that I don&rsquo;t use, either one because I didn&rsquo;t know about them and should be using them or because I already have existing muscle memory that I don&rsquo;t feel like overwriting (from years of using other apps).</p>
<h3 id="things-i-should-use">Things I should use</h3>
<ul>
<li>Open current clipboard url in the current tab p
<ul>
<li>New Tab is Shift + P</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Tab Left, Shift + J</li>
<li>Tab Right, Shift + K</li>
<li>Back
<ul>
<li>Command + [</li>
<li>Shift + H</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Forward
<ul>
<li>Command + ]</li>
<li>Shift + L</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Open a new tab
<ul>
<li>Command + L, or Command + T</li>
<li>o or Shift + O</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="things-i-have-muscle-memory-for-but-are-a-good-idea-to-learn-if-you-dont-already-have-keyboard-shortcuts-memorized">Things I have muscle memory for, but are a good idea to learn if you don&rsquo;t already have keyboard shortcuts memorized</h3>
<ul>
<li>Or gi, I&rsquo;m used to just hitting tab.
Close Tabs</li>
<li>Command + W
<ul>
<li>or with Vimium you can use x</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Reopen the last tab
<ul>
<li>Command + Shift + T</li>
<li>or Shift + X</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>yy to copy the current url to the clipboard
<ul>
<li>I do cmd+l, cmd+c but this I should embrace this one</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="excludes">Excludes</h3>
<p>Exclude R &amp; Escape from all pages (especially my own as they are useful)</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Figma</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><input checked="" disabled="" type="checkbox"> Look up what my excludes are currently</p>
</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>5 Tips for using your mouse less on MacOS</title><link>https://brandonkboswell.com/blog/5-Tips-for-using-your-mouse-less-on-MacOS/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 22:33:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonkboswell.com/blog/5-Tips-for-using-your-mouse-less-on-MacOS/</guid><description>#1. Use a Window Manager I use Amethyst to give specific Monitors and windows focus which was a common thing I would have to pick up my mouse for Hyper + ZXCV for moving Windows Around Hyper + ASDF to move focus #2.</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2 id="1-use-a-window-manager">#1. Use a Window Manager</h2>
<ul>
<li>I use Amethyst to give specific Monitors and windows focus which was a common thing I would have to pick up my mouse for</li>
<li><strong>Hyper + ZXCV</strong> for moving Windows Around</li>
<li><strong>Hyper + ASDF</strong> to move focus</li>
</ul>
<hr>
<h2 id="2-learn-text-cursor-movement">#2. Learn Text Cursor movement</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>Command + Right or Left</strong> to jump to the end of the line</li>
<li><strong>Alt + Right or Left</strong> to move a word at a time
<ul>
<li><strong>Add shift</strong> to select the word while you&rsquo;re at it</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<hr>
<h2 id="3-scroll-with-your-arrow-keys">#3. Scroll with your arrow keys</h2>
<ul>
<li>Most websites let you use up &amp; down arrow keys</li>
<li>I use <strong>Hyper + HJKL</strong> as my arrow keys so that I don&rsquo;t have to leave the home row <em>(optional)</em>
<ul>
<li>You can also use the Vimium Chrome Extension to do this and much more.</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<hr>
<h2 id="4-learn-your-keyboard-shortcuts">#4. Learn your keyboard shortcuts</h2>
<ul>
<li>MacOS Keyboard Shortcuts</li>
<li>App-Specific Keyboard Shortcuts</li>
</ul>
<hr>
<h2 id="macos-keyboard-shortcuts">MacOS Keyboard Shortcuts</h2>
<ul>
<li>Change active application with <strong>Alt + Tab</strong></li>
<li><strong>Ctrl + Cmd + F</strong> for Full Screen</li>
<li>Changing Spaces with <strong>Ctrl + Left or Right</strong></li>
<li>Make sure you know how to play/pause your music &amp; change volume with keyboard shortcuts</li>
<li><strong>Function + Backspace</strong> functions as a forward delete key</li>
<li><strong>Cmd + Shift + 3 or 4</strong> for Screenshots</li>
<li>Close current window with <strong>Cmd + W</strong></li>
<li>Close current app with <strong>Cmd + Q</strong></li>
</ul>
<hr>
<h2 id="app-specific-shortcuts">App-Specific Shortcuts</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>Slack</strong>
<ul>
<li><strong>Command+K</strong> to find conversations</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><strong>Chrome</strong>
<ul>
<li><strong>Cmd + L</strong> to highlight to URL bar</li>
<li><strong>Ctrl + Tab</strong> to switch tabs</li>
<li><strong>Cmd + R</strong> to refresh the current tab</li>
<li><strong>Cmd + [ to go back and CMD + ]</strong> to go forward a page</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<hr>
<h2 id="5-figure-out-how-to-jump-to-your-commonly-used-apps">#5. Figure out how to jump to your commonly used apps</h2>
<ul>
<li>Use Karabiner Elements and add Launchkeys</li>
<li>Use Alfred/Spotlight to help with launch random applications</li>
</ul>
<hr>
<h2 id="exercise">Exercise</h2>
<p><em>If you want to get serious about this write down or keep a mental note of every time you stop &amp; pick up your mouse today.</em></p>
<p><em>Capture what you were trying to do.</em></p>
]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>How I use TickTick 2021</title><link>https://brandonkboswell.com/blog/How-I-use-TickTick-2021/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Oct 2021 11:55:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonkboswell.com/blog/How-I-use-TickTick-2021/</guid><description>Don’t play “catch and release” with your thoughts. Your ideas have value, but tend to arrive when you least expect them. By making it a habit to “capture” and save them, you can allow them to live forever in a trusted system that reflects your goals and interests.</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<blockquote>
<p>Don’t play “catch and release” with your thoughts. Your ideas have value, but tend to arrive when you least expect them. By making it a habit to “capture” and save them, you can allow them to live forever in a trusted system that reflects your goals and interests. This also leaves your mind free and clear to come up with even more ideas.</p>
</blockquote>
<h2 id="-thiago-forte">— Thiago Forte</h2>
<hr>
<h3 id="quick-capture">Quick Capture</h3>
<p>I get ideas &amp; inspiration often while working on others and TickTick&rsquo;s quick capture allows me to quickly jot that down and get back to what I was doing without missing a beat.
* From iOS
* From MacOS
* From Chrome</p>
<h3 id="the-inbox">The Inbox</h3>
<p>My digital note list. This is where I cull through all the things &amp; set follow up timing and lists for.</p>
<p>Reference Seth Godin&rsquo;s work around a system over outcomes. You have control over showing up, you have less control over the outcome, but if you create a system where you produce consistently and are constantly working on improving, you will be doing what you can.</p>
<h3 id="my-lists">My Lists</h3>
<ul>
<li>What are they:
<ul>
<li>Strategic Work vs Junk Work</li>
<li>Routines</li>
<li>Home</li>
<li>Evening</li>
<li>Personal Development</li>
<li>Youtube
<ul>
<li>Youtube Channel</li>
<li>Youtube Video Ideas</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Productivity Blog</li>
<li>Reviews</li>
<li>Family</li>
<li>Store</li>
<li>Content Backlog</li>
<li>Ideas</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="routines">Routines</h3>
<p>Prior to embracing a digital todo list, I was a very reactionary person. Things didn&rsquo;t get done until I noticed they were needed. For example in my twenties I wouldn&rsquo;t go and get a haircut until I realized that my hair was way too long. In my mid twenties I finally realized the value of pre-scheduling haircuts and how I didn&rsquo;t have to look like a bum between haircuts.
Once I figured this out I could apply this same pattern to other things in life. Cutting the dog&rsquo;s nails, changing air filters in the house, getting the car inspected, etc.
Setting up repeats when creating routines.</p>
<h3 id="calendar-view--time-blocking">Calendar View / Time Blocking</h3>
<ul>
<li>How I do my timeblocking and make sure that my plan for the day makes sense. In a perfect world I would review this each night in preparation for the next day, but I typically review this with my morning cup of coffee before work.</li>
<li>Time blocking, including thinking time. Articles. Anything I want to get done. There is a much greater chance that you will follow through on your thinking time if you put it on a calendar. I used to do this in Fantastical, but I found that if I had to move that time for whatever reason (it happened a lot) that I would get phantom notifications and it quickly got the point that I was hating <em>Fantastical</em>. I worked with their support team, but ultimately it sounds like a limitation in how their push notification implementation with iOS and it wasn&rsquo;t fixable. So I solved this by moving my 





<a
  href="/Timeblocking/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/Timeblocking/">Timeblocking</a> to TickTick as it could represent my Google Calendars similarly to Fantastical. (It does have a less than desirable quirk where declined meetings will continue to show). TickTick I&rsquo;ve reported this (please fix it).</li>
</ul>
<hr>
<h3 id="pros">Pros</h3>
<ul>
<li>Has Calendar Support that Things 3 was (intentionally) missing which made timeboxing and aligning with meeting schedules challenging</li>
<li>Really good support for attachments
(this was legitimately the thing that made me leave Things 3)</li>
<li>Syncing between multiple devices
<ul>
<li>Native + Web</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Excellent Quick Capture</li>
<li>Foldered Lists are pretty useful</li>
<li>Free Tier will likely work for many people</li>
</ul>
<hr>
<h3 id="cons">Cons</h3>
<ul>
<li>Template support exists, but is a bit clunky</li>
<li>Invites you decline still show up in TickTick. This is especially painful for weekly recurring meetings. (Fix this TickTick)</li>
<li>You can&rsquo;t move calendar events the way you can tasks, so you still need to use another calendar app such as Fantastical or Google Cal</li>
<li>Calendar view is more readable in the Browser than on the Mac App
<ul>
<li>The difference used to be huge, now it&rsquo;s just minor.</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Save Chrome Tab Groups with Tabox</title><link>https://brandonkboswell.com/blog/Save-Chrome-Tab-Groups-with-Tabox/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2021 08:07:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonkboswell.com/blog/Save-Chrome-Tab-Groups-with-Tabox/</guid><description>Tabox
What is it Tabox is a better version of Tab Groups for Chrome I think they support Edge as well (but I don&amp;rsquo;t use Edge) It solves for me the problem of needing to keep a set of tabs around forever because I&amp;rsquo;m not done with it yet Perhaps I was configuring a new Care Plan at Work, but then I had to run to a meeting.</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>





<a
  href="/Tabox/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/Tabox/">Tabox</a></p>
<h2 id="what-is-it">What is it</h2>
<ul>
<li>Tabox is a better version of Tab Groups for Chrome
<ul>
<li>I think they support Edge as well (but I don&rsquo;t use Edge)</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>It solves for me the problem of needing to keep a set of tabs around forever because I&rsquo;m not done with it yet
<ul>
<li>Perhaps I was configuring a new Care Plan at Work, but then I had to run to a meeting. Before I had to leave all of those tabs open. Or worse if I didn&rsquo;t finish something at the end of the day I would have to decide if I wanted to leave that open overnight or not. At Dorsata users (especially admins) are logged out after inactivity so those tabs aren&rsquo;t going to work in the morning anyway.</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>So how do you use it?
<ul>
<li>Install the Chrome Extension:</li>
<li>Find a set of Tab&rsquo;s you will need to retrieve in the future</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Mouseless MacOS Window Management - Yabai vs Amethyst</title><link>https://brandonkboswell.com/blog/Mouseless-MacOS-Window-Management-Yabai-vs-Amethyst/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Oct 2021 21:13:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonkboswell.com/blog/Mouseless-MacOS-Window-Management-Yabai-vs-Amethyst/</guid><description>Why do you need a window manager at all? too much time moving windows around and wanted an easier way to snap two windows side by side or have a window be full screen without having to us MacOS spaces.</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h3 id="why-do-you-need-a-window-manager-at-all">Why do you need a window manager at all?</h3>
<ul>
<li>too much time moving windows around and wanted an easier way to snap two windows side by side or have a window be full screen without having to us 





<a
  href="/MacOS/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/MacOS/">MacOS</a> spaces.</li>
</ul>
<h3 id="what-have-i-tried">What have I tried?</h3>
<ul>
<li>I used <em>ShiftIt</em> for a number of years</li>
<li>I had 4 basic shortcuts that I would use all the time
<ul>
<li>Left</li>
<li>Right</li>
<li>Full-Screen</li>
<li>Next Monitor</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Worked well, but I found that to do most interactions I was doing I ended up needing the mouse to complete them. For example, putting two windows side-by-side would require a mouse to switch focus reliably to the other monitor.</li>
<li>I found out that <em>ShiftIt</em> was looking for a new maintainer and they were recommending 





<a
  href="/Hammerspoon/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/Hammerspoon/">Hammerspoon</a>.</li>
<li>Eventually I heard about 





<a
  href="/Yabai/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/Yabai/">Yabai</a> and gave it a try. It was very different to what I was using with <em>ShiftIt</em>, but gave a different perspective of window management. Instead of me managing my windows manually, what if they could manage themselves.</li>
<li>I liked the idea of this, but found it to be a bit unreliable in the 





<a
  href="/MacOS/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/MacOS/">MacOS</a> Monterrey Beta which I was running, and started trying to troubleshoot it. I found that <em>BetterTouchTool</em> and it were having weird interactions, and once I stopped using <em>BetterTouchTool</em> it worked better.</li>
<li>While trying to troubleshoot Yabai, I came across Christopher Kapic&rsquo;s Video on Yabai and he mentioned 





<a
  href="/Amethyst/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/Amethyst/">Amethyst</a>. I dug into it and gave it a shot and it seemed to match my needs pretty well.</li>
<li>Here are the shortcuts I use (Note I use a hyper key caps locks that is bound to Escape on tap and changes my HJKL keys into arrow keys). This works well for me not needing to leave the home row, but your mileage may vary.
<ul>
<li>Two Layouts: Tall + Fullscreen
<ul>
<li>This lets me toggle between tiled and fullscreen which is a habit I have from my <em>ShiftIt</em> days</li>
<li>Hyper + Return: Toggle Layout</li>
<li>Shrink &amp; Expand The Layout with Hyper Plus &amp; Minus</li>
<li>Move window focus with Hyper ASDF
<ul>
<li>S &amp; D move the focus forward and back on the active window</li>
<li>A &amp; F move focus to the previous and next monitors accordingly</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Move Windows with Hyper + ZXCV
<ul>
<li>X &amp; C move windows around on the current screen</li>
<li>Z &amp; V move windows to previous and next monitor</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Lastly in order to minimize having to grab my mouse, I set up <em>O Launching</em> with Karabiner Elements for my most common apps
<ul>
<li>Slack</li>
<li>TickTick</li>
<li>Sublime</li>
<li>Chrome</li>
<li>Fantastical</li>
<li>Finder</li>
<li>Spotify</li>
<li>Zoom</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Recently turned off my Dock with 





<a
  href="/TinkerTool/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/TinkerTool/">TinkerTool</a>
<ul>
<li>The dock being visible was required for me up until about a month ago when I tried TinkerTool and was able to make it so that it would quickly show on demand.</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Always show scrollbars on Mac</title><link>https://brandonkboswell.com/blog/Always-show-scrollbars-on-Mac/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 14:13:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonkboswell.com/blog/Always-show-scrollbars-on-Mac/</guid><description>On macOS by default, scrollbar UI is only shown when they are hovered or the page is actively being scrolled. This is a clever way to declutter the UI, but is not consistent with the behavior you will find on Windows.</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On 





<a
  href="/MacOS/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/MacOS/">macOS</a> by default, scrollbar UI is only shown when they are hovered or the page is actively being scrolled. This is a clever way to declutter the UI, but is not consistent with the behavior you will find on Windows. If you are a designer of sites that will be used by both 





<a
  href="/MacOS/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/MacOS/">macOS</a> and <em>Windows</em>, it is a good idea to turn on always visible scrollbars.</p>
<p>At 





<a
  href="/Dorsata/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/Dorsata/">Dorsata</a>, 90+% of our users are on <em>Windows</em>, but our entire engineering and design team is on 





<a
  href="/MacOS/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/MacOS/">macOS</a>. I&rsquo;m not going to push for them to move to <em>Windows</em> (because that would be silly), but we can at least make sure we see something similar to what they see when designing and building apps for them.</p>
<p>For more details on the differences between scrollbars on the Mac and Windows check out 

<a target=“_blank” href="https://gist.github.com/martynchamberlin/6aaf8a45b36907e9f1e21a28889f6b0a" rel="noopener">https://gist.github.com/martynchamberlin/6aaf8a45b36907e9f1e21a28889f6b0a</a>.</p>
<h3 id="steps">Steps</h3>
<ol>
<li>Go to Mac <strong>System Preferences</strong></li>
<li>Choose <strong>General</strong></li>
<li>Under Show Scroll Bars, Choose <strong>Always</strong></li>
<li><strong>Log Out</strong> or <strong>Restart</strong> for the changes be reflected</li>
</ol>
<p>

<img src="/../files/Pasted_Image_10_1_21__2_14_PM.png" alt="Pasted_Image_10_1_21__2_14_PM.png"  /></p>
]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Quickly Mark Up Mac Screenshots on iPad (Skitch vs Markup)</title><link>https://brandonkboswell.com/blog/Quickly-Mark-Up-Mac-Screenshots-on-iPad-Skitch-vs-Markup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 21:57:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonkboswell.com/blog/Quickly-Mark-Up-Mac-Screenshots-on-iPad-Skitch-vs-Markup/</guid><description/><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title>Faster Quick Capture &amp; Dictation for TickTick (iOS)</title><link>https://brandonkboswell.com/blog/Faster-Quick-Capture-Dictation-for-TickTick-iOS/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Sep 2021 21:24:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonkboswell.com/blog/Faster-Quick-Capture-Dictation-for-TickTick-iOS/</guid><description>I started using TickTick in march of this year after finding that time blocking in Things 3 + Fantastical to have a number of issues (perhaps I will do more on that in a future video).</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I started using TickTick in march of this year after finding that time blocking in Things 3 + Fantastical to have a number of issues (perhaps I will do more on that in a future video).</p>
<p>Once I migrated over to TickTick, I found myself using it for everything. It basically became my inbox for everything: Tasks, Ideas, Funny things that people said that I didn&rsquo;t want to instantly forget. I came to the realization that as long as I could get the item into TickTick I would act on it.</p>
<p>The issue I found was although TickTick has good quick capture and dictation built in, there was no way they could do it fast enough for what I wanted. Mostly because of limitations in iOS. At least on my iPhone XS it can only boot so fast and it only can be ready for input so fast.</p>
<p>So I set out to see if I could create a quick capture that was instantly ready for input and that I could easily dictate to while in the shower or driving in the car.</p>
<p>Here&rsquo;s where I landed:</p>
<ul>
<li>Tap Quick Capture: to type in a quick task</li>
<li>I could tap the same for Dictate</li>
<li>If I&rsquo;m in another app and realize there&rsquo;s something I need to do late I can double tap the back of my phone to open the quick capture.</li>
<li>Lastly if I&rsquo;m in driving in the car or get an idea while in the shower I can say Hey Siri, Jot</li>
</ul>
<p>Alright so let me show you how to set this up:
Quick Capture</p>
<p>The Dictation Workflow</p>
<ul>
<li>New Shortcut</li>
<li>Choose a New: In this case Jot this Down</li>
<li>Choose Add Action
<ul>
<li>Search for Dictate Text</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Search for TickTick
<ul>
<li>Choose Add Single Task and Choose Dictated Text</li>
<li>Spin open the Options Arrow and be sure to Enable Edit in App. An interesting issue with Shortcut workflows is they don&rsquo;t open the app and the apps don&rsquo;t get a chance to send your newly created item to the cloud which means your newly created item only exists on your device which is exactly what we don&rsquo;t want. If you choose Edit in App then TickTick will open and your item will be available anywhere you access TickTick.</li>
<li>From here you can hit the share button at the bottom and choose Add to Home Screen
<ul>
<li>You can change the icon by tapping here on the left and you can change the App name here on the right. Choose add and you&rsquo;ve got a Quick Capture App you can launch from the Home Screen</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<p>Alright on to the Quick Capture Workflow:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Same initial steps as before</p>
<ul>
<li>New Shortcut</li>
<li>Name it</li>
<li>Choose Add Action
<ul>
<li>Search for TickTick</li>
<li>Add a Single Task
<ul>
<li>Tap where it says task and choose Ask Each Time. Press Done on your keyboard</li>
<li>Spin open the arrow and enable edit in App</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Lets give it a spin.</li>
<li>If it asks would you like to Allow Your shortcut to share data with TickTick then choose Allow</li>
<li>To make it launch on Double tapping the back of your phone:
<ul>
<li>Go to settings -&gt; Accessibility -&gt; Touch -&gt; Back Tap -&gt;. Double Tap  and choose your Shortcut from the bottom of the list.</li>
<li>Now Double tapping the back of your iPhone will launch your quick capture shortcut.</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<p>There you have it. That&rsquo;s how I quick capture and dictate with TickTick for iOS. If this was helpful to you please leave a like and comment. Also I have a video on how I use Alfred to Quick launch anything. You can check it out right here.</p>
</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Launch anything on your Mac with Alfred</title><link>https://brandonkboswell.com/blog/Launch-anything-on-your-Mac-with-Alfred/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 22:34:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonkboswell.com/blog/Launch-anything-on-your-Mac-with-Alfred/</guid><description>I started using Alfred back in 2014 and It&amp;rsquo;s been a critical part of my Mac OS workflow ever since. I&amp;rsquo;m not going to get into everything that&amp;rsquo;s magical about Alfred because I could ramble way too long about that.</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I started using Alfred back in 2014 and It&rsquo;s been a critical part of my Mac OS workflow ever since. I&rsquo;m not going to get into everything that&rsquo;s magical about Alfred because I could ramble way too long about that. Today let&rsquo;s focus on one particular trick for Alfred which is Bookmarks.</p>
<p>I use 





<a
  href="/Alfred/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/Alfred/">Alfred</a> to open Applications all of the time by tapping Option + Space and typing the application I am looking for, but more and more often the applications I use each day are in my web browser, especially the ones that I work on and have to administer.
Often times there are unique URLs for pages I use, but maybe only once or twice a month.</p>
<p>Wherever possible I want to remove looking from things from my workflow and instead I want to be able to find and launch those things as quickly as I can think of them. What I&rsquo;ve found recently is I can organize my bookmarks by my logical name for them. Basically what I would call them.</p>
<p>If I wanted to get to:</p>
<ul>
<li>the active sprint view in Jira can just type Active</li>
<li>Calendar for <em>Google Calendar</em></li>
<li>Any commonly used page for work
I can put all of those things in a <em>Bookmark</em> folder and call upon them in Alfred.</li>
</ul>
<p>To set it up, just open your Alfred Preferences and then choosing Web Bookmarks
Mark sure your preferred browser is checked and mark sure it&rsquo;s set to in Default Results.
This last option is just personal preference.</p>
<p>From here, Alfred can access your browser&rsquo;s bookmarks and keeps them in sync. If you add a new bookmark just hit Option + Space to open Alfred and then press escape and by the time you open it the next time your newly added bookmark will be there.</p>
<p>Ever since I learned this trick, I feel like I can now get to all the places on my Mac that I want as soon as I think of them. Previously, this was only possible for applications.</p>
]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Calendar Heatmaps</title><link>https://brandonkboswell.com/blog/Calendar-Heatmaps/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 23:47:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonkboswell.com/blog/Calendar-Heatmaps/</guid><description>User Behavior
1 2 3 4 https://github.com/wa0x6e/cal-heatmap Could show one color for having opened at least one chart and a different color for did they take the desired action. https://levelup.</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><em>User Behavior</em></p>
<div class="highlight"><div class="chroma">
<table class="lntable"><tr><td class="lntd">
<pre tabindex="0" class="chroma"><code><span class="lnt">1
</span><span class="lnt">2
</span><span class="lnt">3
</span><span class="lnt">4
</span></code></pre></td>
<td class="lntd">
<pre tabindex="0" class="chroma"><code class="language-fallback" data-lang="fallback">https://github.com/wa0x6e/cal-heatmap
Could show one color for having opened at least one chart and a different color for did they take the desired action. 
https://levelup.gitconnected.com/how-to-create-a-tracker-like-the-github-contribution-graph-with-node-js-and-google-sheets-5e915c668c1
https://github.com/austenc/habitgrid
</code></pre></td></tr></table>
</div>
</div><p>-&gt; This looks like what we&rsquo;re looking for:	https://github.com/MohamedKiouaz/LoopHabitTrackerVisualisation
Reverse Engineer: 

<a target=“_blank” href="https://github.com/Darakah/obsidian-activity-history" rel="noopener">https://github.com/Darakah/obsidian-activity-history</a>
dig into JS heatmaps</p>
<p>Time-series calendar heatmaps / date heatmaps


<a target=“_blank” href="https://www.vertex42.com/ExcelTemplates/calendar-chart.html" rel="noopener">https://www.vertex42.com/ExcelTemplates/calendar-chart.html</a>


<a target=“_blank” href="https://developers.google.com/chart/interactive/docs/gallery/calendar" rel="noopener">https://developers.google.com/chart/interactive/docs/gallery/calendar</a> &lt;- CC: Attribution 4.0</p>
<h2 id="httpscal-heatmapcom---this-is-the-one">

<a target=“_blank” href="https://cal-heatmap.com/" rel="noopener">https://cal-heatmap.com/</a> &lt;- this is the one.</h2>
]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Setting up a new Mac</title><link>https://brandonkboswell.com/blog/Setting-up-a-new-Mac/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2021 15:38:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonkboswell.com/blog/Setting-up-a-new-Mac/</guid><description>MacOS
When Possible Start from a fresh install
Log in to iCloud
Install
Chrome Alfred Obsidian ShiftIt ( Amethyst) aText Skitch Rocket 1Password HandMirror Karabiner Elements Set Karabiner Elements Profile TickTick / Things 3 Fantastical For Development</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>





<a
  href="/MacOS/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/MacOS/">MacOS</a></p>
<ul>
<li>
<p><input checked="" disabled="" type="checkbox"> When Possible Start from a fresh install</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><input checked="" disabled="" type="checkbox"> Log in to <em>iCloud</em></p>
</li>
<li>
<p><input checked="" disabled="" type="checkbox"> Install</p>
<ul>
<li><input checked="" disabled="" type="checkbox"> <em>Chrome</em></li>
<li><input checked="" disabled="" type="checkbox"> 





<a
  href="/Alfred/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/Alfred/">Alfred</a></li>
<li><input checked="" disabled="" type="checkbox"> 





<a
  href="/Obsidian/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/Obsidian/">Obsidian</a></li>
<li><input checked="" disabled="" type="checkbox"> <del><em>ShiftIt</em></del> (





<a
  href="/Amethyst/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/Amethyst/">Amethyst</a>)</li>
<li><input checked="" disabled="" type="checkbox"> <em>aText</em></li>
<li><input checked="" disabled="" type="checkbox"> <em>Skitch</em></li>
<li><input checked="" disabled="" type="checkbox"> 





<a
  href="/Rocket/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/Rocket/">Rocket</a></li>
<li><input checked="" disabled="" type="checkbox"> <em>1Password</em></li>
<li><input checked="" disabled="" type="checkbox"> <em>HandMirror</em></li>
<li><input checked="" disabled="" type="checkbox"> <em>Karabiner Elements</em>
<ul>
<li><input checked="" disabled="" type="checkbox"> Set <em>Karabiner Elements</em> Profile</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><input checked="" disabled="" type="checkbox"> 





<a
  href="/TickTick/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/TickTick/">TickTick</a> / <em>Things 3</em></li>
<li><input checked="" disabled="" type="checkbox"> <em>Fantastical</em></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<p><input checked="" disabled="" type="checkbox"> For Development</p>
<ul>
<li><input checked="" disabled="" type="checkbox"> <em>Postico</em></li>
<li><input checked="" disabled="" type="checkbox"> <em>Sublime Text</em></li>
<li><input checked="" disabled="" type="checkbox"> 





<a
  href="/iTerm2/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/iTerm2/">iTerm2</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<p><input checked="" disabled="" type="checkbox"> Configure</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p><input checked="" disabled="" type="checkbox"> Mouse/Trackpad</p>
<ul>
<li><input checked="" disabled="" type="checkbox"> Turn off natural direction</li>
<li><input checked="" disabled="" type="checkbox"> Turn off Force touch</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<p><input checked="" disabled="" type="checkbox"> Setup Key Repeat (Maybe just run the dotfiles)</p>
<blockquote>
<p>defaults write -g InitialKeyRepeat -int 10 # normal minimum is 15 (225 ms)
defaults write -g KeyRepeat -int 1 # normal minimum is 2 (30 ms)</p>
</blockquote>
</li>
<li>
<p><input checked="" disabled="" type="checkbox"> Or Just use 





<a
  href="/TinkerTool/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/TinkerTool/">TinkerTool</a></p>
</li>
<li>
<p><input checked="" disabled="" type="checkbox"> Show Battery</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><input checked="" disabled="" type="checkbox"> Hide Siri</p>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<p>Setting Up Dev Environment</p>
<ul>
<li><input checked="" disabled="" type="checkbox"> 





<a
  href="/iTerm2/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/iTerm2/">iTerm2</a></li>
<li><input checked="" disabled="" type="checkbox"> <em>Sublime Text</em>
<ul>
<li><input checked="" disabled="" type="checkbox"> Get Preferences</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<p>My <em>dotfiles</em> are available at 

<a target=“_blank” href="https://github.com/brandonkboswell/dotfiles" rel="noopener">https://github.com/brandonkboswell/dotfiles</a></p>
]]></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>