<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Brandon Boswell</title><link>https://brandonkboswell.com/tags/status/needs_article/</link><description>Recent content from Brandon Boswell's Digital Garden</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://brandonkboswell.com/tags/status/needs_article/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Timeblocking</title><link>https://brandonkboswell.com/Timeblocking/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2022 11:48:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonkboswell.com/Timeblocking/</guid><description>In my head there are two types of timeblocking and I am realizing that I&amp;rsquo;m not sure which one people are talking about when they mention the subject. There is the idea of thinking about how much time a task will take and slotting that into available time on your daily or weekly schedule to figure out what will fit and what you will prioritize.</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In my head there are two types of timeblocking and I am realizing that I&rsquo;m not sure which one people are talking about when they mention the subject. There is the idea of thinking about how much time a task will take and slotting that into available time on your daily or weekly schedule to figure out what will fit and what you will prioritize. Then there is also the idea of blocking time on your schedule for doing a specific type of work or a specific task so that others don&rsquo;t attempt to schedule over your 





<a
  
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link broken"
  data-src="seedlings/There%20is%20a%20two%20hour%20window%20in%20each%20day%20where%20you%20are%20most%20productive.">Most productive time of the day</a>. I think both are important and we should be discussing both, but I now no longer know which one people are referring to when we use the term.</p>
<p><strong>Is there another term we should be using talking about holding time on your calendar to fulfill your role (<em>Defending your schedule</em>)?</strong></p>
]]></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>