<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Brandon Boswell</title><link>https://brandonkboswell.com/tags/status/review/</link><description>Recent content from Brandon Boswell's Digital Garden</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://brandonkboswell.com/tags/status/review/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Explain how you approach the problem instead of trying to answer the question</title><link>https://brandonkboswell.com/Explain-how-you-approach-the-problem-instead-of-trying-to-answer-the-question/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 10:34:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonkboswell.com/Explain-how-you-approach-the-problem-instead-of-trying-to-answer-the-question/</guid><description/><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title>Incremental Note Taking</title><link>https://brandonkboswell.com/Incremental-Note-Taking/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 08:23:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonkboswell.com/Incremental-Note-Taking/</guid><description>Ideas should not be lost because it took too long to capture them in the moment. Our tools most be accessed quickly and in an unburdensome way. Don&amp;rsquo;t erase past thoughts that are now outdated, they capture your journey and the journey that many others will likely take after you.</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<ol>
<li>





<a
  href="/Ideas-should-not-be-lost-because-it-took-too-long-to-capture-them/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/Ideas-should-not-be-lost-because-it-took-too-long-to-capture-them/">Ideas should not be lost because it took too long to capture them</a> in the moment. Our tools most be accessed quickly and in an unburdensome way.</li>
<li>





<a
  href="/Dont-erase-past-thoughts-that-are-now-outdated-they-capture-your-journey/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/Dont-erase-past-thoughts-that-are-now-outdated-they-capture-your-journey/">Don&rsquo;t erase past thoughts that are now outdated, they capture your journey</a> and the journey that many others will likely take after you. (WIP notes should be largely immutable)</li>
<li>You need a system to revisit these notes or they might as well not exist. 





<a
  
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link broken"
  data-src="sources/Inboxes%20Only%20Work%20if%20You%20Trust%20How%20They%E2%80%99re%20Drained">Inboxes Only Work if You Trust How They’re Drained</a></li>
<li>





<a
  href="/Time-is-essential-to-how-we-remember-and-should-be-a-first-class-concept-in-a-good-note-taking-system/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/Time-is-essential-to-how-we-remember-and-should-be-a-first-class-concept-in-a-good-note-taking-system/">Time is essential to how we remember, and should be a first-class concept in a good note-taking system</a>.</li>
</ol>
<h3 id="references">References</h3>
<p>





<a
  
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link broken"
  data-src="sources/Incremental%20Note-Taking%20%20thesephist.com">Incremental Note-Taking  thesephist.com</a></p>
]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>B-Roll</title><link>https://brandonkboswell.com/B-Roll/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 12:30:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonkboswell.com/B-Roll/</guid><description>Zoom in on the aspect we&amp;rsquo;re trying to show and then Zoom out. B-Roll Ideas Zoom In
Pan Across
Crop In
iPad</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<ul>
<li><input disabled="" type="checkbox"> Zoom in on the aspect we&rsquo;re trying to show and then Zoom out.</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="b-roll-ideas">B-Roll Ideas</h2>
<ul>
<li>
<p><input disabled="" type="checkbox"> Zoom In</p>
<p>Pan Across</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><input disabled="" type="checkbox"> Crop In</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><input disabled="" type="checkbox"> iPad</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><input disabled="" type="checkbox"> Over the Shoulder</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><input disabled="" type="checkbox"> How you use it from your desk</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><input disabled="" type="checkbox"> Side Shot</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><input disabled="" type="checkbox"> Inverse Shot</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><input disabled="" type="checkbox"> Homepage of whatever you&rsquo;re talking about</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><input disabled="" type="checkbox"> Desk Setup</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><input disabled="" type="checkbox"> Off Angle (Could you do this in post?)</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><input disabled="" type="checkbox"> Sketching</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><input disabled="" type="checkbox"> Chapter Breakups</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><input disabled="" type="checkbox"> Show the Channel</p>
</li>
<li>
<p><input disabled="" type="checkbox"> End Screen (Animates in)</p>
</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Four Thousand Weeks</title><link>https://brandonkboswell.com/sources/Four-Thousand-Weeks/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 10:40:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonkboswell.com/sources/Four-Thousand-Weeks/</guid><description>Four Thousand Weeks Metadata Author: Oliver Burkeman Full Title: Four Thousand Weeks Highlights good luck finding a time management system that makes any room for engaging productively with your fellow citizens, with current events, or with the fate of the environment.</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1 id="four-thousand-weeks">Four Thousand Weeks</h1>
<p>
<img src="https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/71udc7ZQtVL._SY160.jpg" alt="rw-book-cover"  /></p>
<h2 id="metadata">Metadata</h2>
<ul>
<li>Author: <em>Oliver Burkeman</em></li>
<li>Full Title: Four Thousand Weeks</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="highlights">Highlights</h2>
<hr>
<p>good luck finding a time management system that makes any room for engaging productively with your fellow citizens, with current events, or with the fate of the environment. (

<a target=“_blank” href="https://readwise.io/to_kindle?action=open&amp;asin=B08FGV64B1&amp;location=57" rel="noopener">Location 57</a>)</p>
<hr>
<p>Take the daily battle against online distraction, and the alarming sense that our attention spans have shriveled to such a degree that even those of us who were bookworms as children now struggle to make it through a paragraph without experiencing the urge to reach for our phones. (

<a target=“_blank” href="https://readwise.io/to_kindle?action=open&amp;asin=B08FGV64B1&amp;location=73" rel="noopener">Location 73</a>)</p>
<hr>
<p>It turns out that when people make enough money to meet their needs, they just find new things to need and new lifestyles to aspire to; they never quite manage to keep up with the Joneses, because whenever they’re in danger of getting close, they nominate new and better Joneses with whom to try to keep up. (

<a target=“_blank” href="https://readwise.io/to_kindle?action=open&amp;asin=B08FGV64B1&amp;location=131" rel="noopener">Location 131</a>)</p>
<p><em>Revolving Joneses Principle</em></p>
<hr>
<p>Edward Hall was making the same point with his image of time as a conveyor belt that’s constantly passing us by. Each hour or week or year is like a container being carried on the belt, which we must fill as it passes, if we’re to feel that we’re making good use of our time. When there are too many activities to fit comfortably into the containers, we feel unpleasantly busy; when there are too few, we feel bored. If we keep pace with the passing containers, we congratulate ourselves for “staying on top of things” and feel like we’re justifying our existence; if we let too many pass by unfilled, we feel we’ve wasted them. If we use containers labeled “work time” for the purposes of leisure, our employer may grow irritated. (

<a target=“_blank” href="https://readwise.io/to_kindle?action=open&amp;asin=B08FGV64B1&amp;location=206" rel="noopener">Location 206</a>)</p>
<p>





<a
  href="/Time-is-a-conveyor-belt/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/Time-is-a-conveyor-belt/">Time is a conveyor belt</a></p>
<hr>
<p>The fundamental problem is that this attitude toward time sets up a rigged game in which it’s impossible ever to feel as though you’re doing well enough. Instead of simply living our lives as they unfold in time—instead of just being time, you might say—it becomes difficult not to value each moment primarily according to its usefulness for some future goal, or for some future oasis of relaxation you hope to reach once your tasks are finally “out of the way.” (

<a target=“_blank” href="https://readwise.io/to_kindle?action=open&amp;asin=B08FGV64B1&amp;location=282" rel="noopener">Location 282</a>)</p>
<hr>
<p>The universal truth behind my specific issues is that most of us invest a lot of energy, one way or another, in trying to avoid fully experiencing the reality in which we find ourselves. We don’t want to feel the anxiety that might arise if we were to ask ourselves whether we’re on the right path, or what ideas about ourselves it could be time to give up. We don’t want to risk getting hurt in relationships or failing professionally; we don’t want to accept that we might never succeed in pleasing our parents or in changing certain things we don’t like about ourselves—and we certainly don’t want to get sick and die. The details differ from person to person, but the kernel is the same. We recoil from the notion that this is it—that this life, with all its flaws and inescapable vulnerabilities, its extreme brevity, and our limited influence over how it unfolds, is the only one we’ll get a shot at. (

<a target=“_blank” href="https://readwise.io/to_kindle?action=open&amp;asin=B08FGV64B1&amp;location=331" rel="noopener">Location 331</a>) #review</p>
<hr>
<p>After all, it’s painful to confront how limited your time is, because it means that tough choices are inevitable and that you won’t have time for all you once dreamed you might do. It’s also painful to accept your limited control over the time you do get: (

<a target=“_blank” href="https://readwise.io/to_kindle?action=open&amp;asin=B08FGV64B1&amp;location=344" rel="noopener">Location 344</a>) #review</p>
<hr>
<p>rather than face our limitations, we engage in avoidance strategies, in an effort to carry on feeling limitless. (

<a target=“_blank” href="https://readwise.io/to_kindle?action=open&amp;asin=B08FGV64B1&amp;location=346" rel="noopener">Location 346</a>) #review</p>
<hr>
<p>the paradox of limitation, which runs through everything that follows: the more you try to manage your time with the goal of achieving a feeling of total control, and freedom from the inevitable constraints of being human, the more stressful, empty, and frustrating life gets. But the more you confront the facts of finitude instead—and work with them, rather than against them—the more productive, meaningful, and joyful life becomes. (

<a target=“_blank” href="https://readwise.io/to_kindle?action=open&amp;asin=B08FGV64B1&amp;location=365" rel="noopener">Location 365</a>) #review</p>
<hr>
<p>a limit-embracing attitude to time means organizing your days with the understanding that you definitely won’t have time for everything you want to do, or that other people want you to do—and so, at the very least, you can stop beating yourself up for failing. (

<a target=“_blank” href="https://readwise.io/to_kindle?action=open&amp;asin=B08FGV64B1&amp;location=372" rel="noopener">Location 372</a>) #review</p>
<hr>
<p>Since hard choices are unavoidable, what matters is learning to make them consciously, deciding what to focus on and what to neglect, rather than letting them get made by default—or deceiving yourself that, with enough hard work and the right time management tricks, you might not have to make them at all. (

<a target=“_blank” href="https://readwise.io/to_kindle?action=open&amp;asin=B08FGV64B1&amp;location=374" rel="noopener">Location 374</a>) #review</p>
<hr>
<p>meaningful productivity often comes not from hurrying things up but from letting them take the time they take, surrendering to what in German has been called Eigenzeit, or the time inherent to a process itself. (

<a target=“_blank” href="https://readwise.io/to_kindle?action=open&amp;asin=B08FGV64B1&amp;location=387" rel="noopener">Location 387</a>) #review</p>
<hr>
<p>There is an alternative: the unfashionable but powerful notion of letting time use you, approaching life not as an opportunity to implement your predetermined plans for success but as a matter of responding to the needs of your place and your moment in history. (

<a target=“_blank” href="https://readwise.io/to_kindle?action=open&amp;asin=B08FGV64B1&amp;location=390" rel="noopener">Location 390</a>) #review</p>
<hr>
<p>As the law professor Daniel Markovits has shown, even the winners in our achievement-obsessed culture—the ones who make it to the elite universities, then reap the highest salaries—find that their reward is the unending pressure to work with “crushing intensity” in order to maintain the income and status that have come to seem like prerequisites for the lives they want to lead. (

<a target=“_blank” href="https://readwise.io/to_kindle?action=open&amp;asin=B08FGV64B1&amp;location=427" rel="noopener">Location 427</a>) #review</p>
<hr>
<p>We rarely stop to consider things so rationally, though, because that would mean confronting the painful truth of our limitations. We would be forced to acknowledge that there are hard choices to be made: which balls to let drop, which people to disappoint, which cherished ambitions to abandon, which roles to fail at. (

<a target=“_blank” href="https://readwise.io/to_kindle?action=open&amp;asin=B08FGV64B1&amp;location=435" rel="noopener">Location 435</a>) #review</p>
<hr>
<p>For a start, what “matters” is subjective, so you’ve no grounds for assuming that there will be time for everything that you, or your employer, or your culture happens to deem important. But the other exasperating issue is that if you succeed in fitting more in, you’ll find the goalposts start to shift: more things will begin to seem important, meaningful, or obligatory. (

<a target=“_blank” href="https://readwise.io/to_kindle?action=open&amp;asin=B08FGV64B1&amp;location=468" rel="noopener">Location 468</a>) #review</p>
<hr>
<p>(By contrast, negligent emailers frequently find that forgetting to reply ends up saving them time: people find alternative solutions to the problems they were nagging you to solve, or the looming crisis they were emailing about never materializes.) (

<a target=“_blank” href="https://readwise.io/to_kindle?action=open&amp;asin=B08FGV64B1&amp;location=495" rel="noopener">Location 495</a>) #review</p>
<hr>
<p>Once you stop believing that it might somehow be possible to avoid hard choices about time, it gets easier to make better ones. (

<a target=“_blank” href="https://readwise.io/to_kindle?action=open&amp;asin=B08FGV64B1&amp;location=510" rel="noopener">Location 510</a>) #review</p>
<hr>
<p>premodern people weren’t much troubled by such thoughts, partly because they believed in an afterlife: there was no particular pressure to “get the most out of” their limited time, because as far as they were concerned, it wasn’t limited, and in any case, earthly life was but a relatively insignificant prelude to the most important part. (

<a target=“_blank” href="https://readwise.io/to_kindle?action=open&amp;asin=B08FGV64B1&amp;location=518" rel="noopener">Location 518</a>) #review</p>
<hr>
<p>because in reality your time is finite, doing anything requires sacrifice—the sacrifice of all the other things you could have been doing with that stretch of time. (

<a target=“_blank” href="https://readwise.io/to_kindle?action=open&amp;asin=B08FGV64B1&amp;location=563" rel="noopener">Location 563</a>) #review</p>
<hr>
<p>Despite my thinking of myself as the kind of person who got things done, it grew painfully clear that the things I got done most diligently were the unimportant ones, while the important ones got postponed—either forever or until an imminent deadline forced me to complete them, to a mediocre standard and in a stressful rush. (

<a target=“_blank” href="https://readwise.io/to_kindle?action=open&amp;asin=B08FGV64B1&amp;location=570" rel="noopener">Location 570</a>) #review</p>
<hr>
<p>Meanwhile, the long message from an old friend now living in New Delhi and research for the major article I’d been planning for months would get ignored, because I told myself that such tasks needed my full focus, which meant waiting until I had a good chunk of free time and fewer small-but-urgent tasks tugging at my attention. And so, instead, like the dutiful and efficient worker I was, I’d put my energy into clearing the decks, cranking through the smaller stuff to get it out of the way—only to discover that doing so took the whole day, that the decks filled up again overnight anyway, and that the moment for responding to the New Delhi email or for researching the milestone article never arrived. One can waste years this way, systematically postponing precisely the things one cares about the most. (

<a target=“_blank” href="https://readwise.io/to_kindle?action=open&amp;asin=B08FGV64B1&amp;location=574" rel="noopener">Location 574</a>) #review</p>
<hr>
<p>Once you truly understand that you’re guaranteed to miss out on almost every experience the world has to offer, the fact that there are so many you still haven’t experienced stops feeling like a problem. Instead, you get to focus on fully enjoying the tiny slice of experiences you actually do have time for—and the freer you are to choose, in each moment, what counts the most. (

<a target=“_blank” href="https://readwise.io/to_kindle?action=open&amp;asin=B08FGV64B1&amp;location=589" rel="noopener">Location 589</a>) #review</p>
<hr>
<p>But we’ve forgotten to be amazed that things are in the first place—that “a world is worlding all around us,” as Heidegger puts it. This fact—the fact that there is being, to begin with—is “the brute reality on which all of us ought to be constantly stubbing our toes,” in the splendid phrase of the writer Sarah Bakewell. (

<a target=“_blank” href="https://readwise.io/to_kindle?action=open&amp;asin=B08FGV64B1&amp;location=676" rel="noopener">Location 676</a>) #review</p>
<hr>
<p>The only real question about all this finitude is whether we’re willing to confront it or not. And this, for Heidegger, is the central challenge of human existence: since finitude defines our lives, he argues that living a truly authentic life—becoming fully human—means facing up to that fact. (

<a target=“_blank” href="https://readwise.io/to_kindle?action=open&amp;asin=B08FGV64B1&amp;location=701" rel="noopener">Location 701</a>) #review</p>
<hr>
<p>What’s really morbid, from this perspective, is what most of us do, most of the time, instead of confronting our finitude, which is to indulge in avoidance and denial, or what Heidegger calls “falling.” Rather than taking ownership of our lives, we seek out distractions, or lose ourselves in busyness and the daily grind, so as to try to forget our real predicament. (

<a target=“_blank” href="https://readwise.io/to_kindle?action=open&amp;asin=B08FGV64B1&amp;location=712" rel="noopener">Location 712</a>) #review</p>
<hr>
<p>If you really thought life would never end, he argues, then nothing could ever genuinely matter, because you’d never be faced with having to decide whether or not to use a portion of your precious life on something. (

<a target=“_blank” href="https://readwise.io/to_kindle?action=open&amp;asin=B08FGV64B1&amp;location=724" rel="noopener">Location 724</a>) #review</p>
<hr>
<p>Or to put it another way, why treat four thousand weeks as a very small number, because it’s so tiny compared with infinity, rather than treating it as a huge number, because it’s so many more weeks than if you had never been born? (

<a target=“_blank” href="https://readwise.io/to_kindle?action=open&amp;asin=B08FGV64B1&amp;location=775" rel="noopener">Location 775</a>) #review</p>
<hr>
<p>I’m embarrassed to admit what an outsize negative effect such minor frustrations have had on my happiness over the years. Fairly often, they still do; but the effect was worst at the height of my productivity geekhood, because when you’re trying to Master Your Time, few things are more infuriating than a task or delay that’s foisted upon you against your will, with no regard for the schedule you’ve painstakingly drawn up in your overpriced notebook. (

<a target=“_blank” href="https://readwise.io/to_kindle?action=open&amp;asin=B08FGV64B1&amp;location=793" rel="noopener">Location 793</a>) #review</p>
<hr>
<p>So the point isn’t to eradicate procrastination, but to choose more wisely what you’re going to procrastinate on, in order to focus on what matters most. The real measure of any time management technique is whether or not it helps you neglect the right things. (

<a target=“_blank” href="https://readwise.io/to_kindle?action=open&amp;asin=B08FGV64B1&amp;location=836" rel="noopener">Location 836</a>) #review</p>
<hr>
<p>the teacher demonstrates the solution: he puts the rocks in first, then the pebbles, then the sand, so that the smaller items nestle comfortably in the spaces between the larger ones. The moral is that if you make time for the most important things first, you’ll get them all done and have plenty of room for less important things besides. But if you don’t approach your to-do list in this order, you’ll never fit the bigger things in at all. (

<a target=“_blank” href="https://readwise.io/to_kindle?action=open&amp;asin=B08FGV64B1&amp;location=844" rel="noopener">Location 844</a>) #review</p>
<hr>
<p>The trouble is that we’re terrible at long-range planning: if something feels like a priority now, it’s virtually impossible to coolly assess whether it will still feel that way in a week or a month. (

<a target=“_blank” href="https://readwise.io/to_kindle?action=open&amp;asin=B08FGV64B1&amp;location=863" rel="noopener">Location 863</a>) #review</p>
<hr>
<p>This is the same insight embodied in two venerable pieces of time management advice: to work on your most important project for the first hour of each day, and to protect your time by scheduling “meetings” with yourself, marking them in your calendar so that other commitments can’t intrude. (

<a target=“_blank” href="https://readwise.io/to_kindle?action=open&amp;asin=B08FGV64B1&amp;location=874" rel="noopener">Location 874</a>) #review</p>
<hr>
<p>The second principle is to limit your work in progress. Perhaps the most appealing way to resist the truth about your finite time is to initiate a large number of projects at once; that way, you get to feel as though you’re keeping plenty of irons in the fire and making progress on all fronts. Instead, what usually ends up happening is that you make progress on no fronts—because each time a project starts to feel difficult, or frightening, or boring, you can bounce off to a different one instead. You get to preserve your sense of being in control of things, but at the cost of never finishing anything important. The alternative approach is to fix a hard upper limit on the number of things that you allow yourself to work on at any given time. In their book Personal Kanban, which explores this strategy in detail, the management experts Jim Benson and Tonianne DeMaria Barry suggest no more than three items. (

<a target=“_blank” href="https://readwise.io/to_kindle?action=open&amp;asin=B08FGV64B1&amp;location=879" rel="noopener">Location 879</a>) #review</p>
<hr>
<p>Another happy consequence was that I found myself effortlessly breaking down my projects into manageable chunks, a strategy I’d long agreed with in theory but never properly implemented. Now it became the intuitive thing to do: it was clear that if I nominated “write book” or “move house” as one of my three tasks in progress, it would clog up the system for months, so I was naturally motivated to figure out the next achievable step in each case instead. Rather than trying to do everything, I found it easier to accept the truth that I’d be doing only a few things on any given day. The difference, this time, was that I actually did them. (

<a target=“_blank” href="https://readwise.io/to_kindle?action=open&amp;asin=B08FGV64B1&amp;location=894" rel="noopener">Location 894</a>) #review</p>
<hr>
<p>We invariably prefer indecision over committing ourselves to a single path, Bergson wrote, because “the future, which we dispose of to our liking, appears to us at the same time under a multitude of forms, equally attractive and equally possible.” In other words, it’s easy for me to fantasize about, say, a life spent achieving stellar professional success, while also excelling as a parent and partner, while also dedicating myself to training for marathons or lengthy meditation retreats or volunteering in my community—because so long as I’m only fantasizing, I get to imagine all of them unfolding simultaneously and flawlessly. As soon as I start trying to live any of those lives, though, I’ll be forced to make trade-offs—to put less time than I’d like into one of those domains, so as to make space for another—and to accept that nothing I do will go perfectly anyway, with the result that my actual life will inevitably prove disappointing by comparison with the fantasy. (

<a target=“_blank” href="https://readwise.io/to_kindle?action=open&amp;asin=B08FGV64B1&amp;location=978" rel="noopener">Location 978</a>) #review</p>
<hr>
<p>having committed themselves to one finite course of action, they’ll be much less likely to spend that time pining after fantastical alternatives. In consciously making a commitment, they’re closing off their fantasies of infinite possibility in favor of what I described, in the previous chapter, as the “joy of missing out”: the recognition that the renunciation of alternatives is what makes their choice a meaningful one in the first place. (

<a target=“_blank” href="https://readwise.io/to_kindle?action=open&amp;asin=B08FGV64B1&amp;location=1040" rel="noopener">Location 1040</a>) #review</p>
<hr>
<p>what you pay attention to will define, for you, what reality is. (

<a target=“_blank” href="https://readwise.io/to_kindle?action=open&amp;asin=B08FGV64B1&amp;location=1071" rel="noopener">Location 1071</a>) #review</p>
<hr>
<p>Attention, on the other hand, just is life: your experience of being alive consists of nothing other than the sum of everything to which you pay attention. (

<a target=“_blank” href="https://readwise.io/to_kindle?action=open&amp;asin=B08FGV64B1&amp;location=1077" rel="noopener">Location 1077</a>) #review</p>
<hr>
<p>the crucial point isn’t that it’s wrong to choose to spend your time relaxing, whether at the beach or on BuzzFeed. It’s that the distracted person isn’t really choosing at all. Their attention has been commandeered by forces that don’t have their highest interests at heart. (

<a target=“_blank” href="https://readwise.io/to_kindle?action=open&amp;asin=B08FGV64B1&amp;location=1088" rel="noopener">Location 1088</a>) #review</p>
]]></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>