<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Brandon Boswell</title><link>https://brandonkboswell.com/tags/rms/s/needs_review/</link><description>Recent content from Brandon Boswell's Digital Garden</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://brandonkboswell.com/tags/rms/s/needs_review/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Managing Notebooks and Documents</title><link>https://brandonkboswell.com/Managing-Notebooks-and-Documents/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 17:15:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonkboswell.com/Managing-Notebooks-and-Documents/</guid><description>So you&amp;rsquo;ve started to accumulate a few notebooks and documents, and they are starting to get out of hand. Let&amp;rsquo;s talk through how we can manage and organize our documents.
In this lesson, we&amp;rsquo;ll talk about creating folders and moving your notebooks around.
In my opinion, the most important concept with any of these devices is to have a concept of an Archive. You need a way to make the documents you&amp;rsquo;re not actively using not clutter your space and leave you overwhelmed. In this lesson I will show you a nice simple way to do this, and in a future lesson I will show you some more exotic ways you can do this once you&amp;rsquo;ve gotten your bearings.</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>So you&rsquo;ve started to accumulate a few notebooks and documents, and they are starting to get out of hand. Let&rsquo;s talk through how we can manage and organize our documents.</p>
<p>In this lesson, we&rsquo;ll talk about creating folders and moving your notebooks around.</p>
<p>In my opinion, the most important concept with any of these devices is to have a concept of an Archive. You need a way to make the documents you&rsquo;re not actively using not clutter your space and leave you overwhelmed. In this lesson I will show you a nice simple way to do this, and in a future lesson I will show you some more exotic ways you can do this once you&rsquo;ve gotten your bearings. The simplest way to do this is to create a simple archive folder. Instead of deleting documents when we&rsquo;re done, we can move them to the archive, and then we if we ever need to revisit them we&rsquo;ll still have them, but we don&rsquo;t need to see them. The other benefit here is the documents we do show on our Home screen will be the ones we&rsquo;re actively using. Let me show you how to set it up:</p>
<ul>
<li>From the top of the <code>My Files</code> menu, there is an option to add a new folder. Tap on that and let&rsquo;s call it Archive. That folder will get added to your Home screen on My Files.</li>
<li>Now whenever you&rsquo;re done with a notebook or document, instead of leaving it on your home screen forever you can move it to the archive. If you try to drag and drop your notebook into the folder you&rsquo;ll find that it doesn&rsquo;t work, but like I showed in the tagging and favoriting lesson, we can tap and hold on a Document to bring up a contextual menu across the top. From here, we just tap <code>Move</code>. From here, you can tap on our newly created Archive folder. Now just choose <code>Move here</code> from the top right. Note that you can also create a folder while in this menu if you didn&rsquo;t already have an Archive folder. If you change your mind, you can always choose cancel from the Top Left. Also note that once you complete or cancel the move, the reMarkable will leave you in that folder and if you would like to get back to your home screen you can do that by tapping the <code>My files</code> breadcrumb just below the menu.</li>
</ul>
<p>Now, if we ever need to revisit an archived note, we can search for them with the magnifying glass in the top right, or we can open this Archive folder and browse around. This is probably a scenario where changing the sort order can be handy. By default, it&rsquo;s going to be set to <code>Last modified</code>, but <code>Last opened</code> could be handy and <code>Alphabetical</code> is also nice.</p>
]]></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>