<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Brandon Boswell</title><link>https://brandonkboswell.com/cooking/</link><description>Recent content from Brandon Boswell's Digital Garden</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 21:30:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://brandonkboswell.com/cooking/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Smoked Spatchcock Chicken</title><link>https://brandonkboswell.com/cooking/Smoked-Spatchcock-Chicken/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 21:30:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonkboswell.com/cooking/Smoked-Spatchcock-Chicken/</guid><description><p><em>2022-03-20</em>
This was my first time using the<em>Char-Griller Akorn</em>. I set an initial fire in the Akorn to get it to 400 degrees to season the grill grate. This worked well, and I had no issues getting the grill to high temperature, even getting it past 500 degrees. I had a minor challenge where I put the fire out while trying to reduce the temperature significantly to get back to a smoking temperature after running it at high heat. After relighting the fire I cooked the chicken between 225 and 275 for an hour and half until the chicken got to an internal temperature of 145 degrees. At the point, I raised the heat to 325 to crisp up the skin and make it easier to get the chicken to temperature. For this chicken we used a KC BBQ rub along with mayonnaise and olive oil on the underside. Initially I didn&rsquo;t put enough seasoning on the chicken, but we later added a bit more. The fire was likely 8 to 2 lump to hickory. The chicken was cooked very nicely, but I found the rub to be too sweet for chicken (its probably better suited for pork). I may try something simpler like just salt and pepper next time to see how that compares. For this cook, we were lacking the smoking stone, but were able to substitute in a baking sheet instead for today. The smoking stone will be here tomorrow along with a thermometer that will talk to my phone so that I can monitor the fire from afar.</p><hr><h3 id="references">References</h3><p><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-JJx4eZNmz4" rel="noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-JJx4eZNmz4</a><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0de3Q9hQSTA" rel="noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0de3Q9hQSTA</a><a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0Y7gM1deyvw&amp;t=1s" rel="noopener">https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0Y7gM1deyvw&t=1s</a></p></description></item><item><title>Brussels Sprouts</title><link>https://brandonkboswell.com/cooking/Brussels-Sprouts/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 08:43:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonkboswell.com/cooking/Brussels-Sprouts/</guid><description><p><em>Cooking</em></p><p><em>2022-01-13</em> Halved until all about the same size. Applied canola oil, salt, pepper and the paprika spice blend. 7 minutes in the air fryer and brown and beginning to soften.</p></description></item><item><title>Skirt Steak</title><link>https://brandonkboswell.com/cooking/Skirt-Steak/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jan 2022 08:38:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonkboswell.com/cooking/Skirt-Steak/</guid><description><p><em>Cooking</em></p><p><em>2022-02-16</em> Same Teriyaki Skirt Steak from Trader Joes. Didn&rsquo;t pat dry and let the steak go for 3 minutes on each side. The result was likely the right about of done-ness.</p><p><em>2022-01-13</em> Teriyaki Skirt Steak from Trader Joes. Heat the pan to high. Take the steak out of the package and get unnecessary liquid off, but didn&rsquo;t not pat dry. Let pan get to make temperature. Likely around 5-7 minute wait time. In this case I halved a bag of brussels sprouts. Add meat to an ungreased pan as the liquid provides enough grease. This time I did 2 minutes per side. I think for next time I should try 2:30. Result: Good sear, perhaps a little too done in places and not enough in others. Perhaps a weight could help to create good contact. The cook was very Medium Rare, could be slightly more done by my standards, but this should largely be a judgement call based on the thickness of the cut. These were reasonably thick by Trader Joe&rsquo;s standard, but if you got a good butchered cut you would need more time.</p></description></item></channel></rss>