<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Brandon Boswell</title><link>https://brandonkboswell.com/tags/status/draft/</link><description>Recent content from Brandon Boswell's Digital Garden</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://brandonkboswell.com/tags/status/draft/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>One Sec</title><link>https://brandonkboswell.com/One-Sec/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 23:56:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonkboswell.com/One-Sec/</guid><description>$19 dollars a year to be more aware of when I am leaking time on Time Sinks.
Cancelled on 2022-04-25. Had signed up for a year subscription to try it out.</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>$19 dollars a year to be more aware of when I am leaking time on 





<a
  href="/Time-Sinks/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/Time-Sinks/">Time Sinks</a>.</p>
<p>Cancelled on <em>2022-04-25</em>. Had signed up for a year subscription to try it out. Turns out I found it incredibly annoying, and I&rsquo;ve instead adopted the principle to set a 5-minute timer to remind myself to get off of whatever app I was on. That was the piece I really enjoyed, and it can be accomplished with a simple Shortcut flow on iOS (similar to what the app uses).</p>
<p>All in all, it was worth it because it showed me how useful that notification can be and how to use app launching intercepts to do interesting actions on iOS.</p>
]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Obsidian</title><link>https://brandonkboswell.com/Obsidian/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 00:51:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonkboswell.com/Obsidian/</guid><description>The application I&amp;rsquo;m writing in at the moment. This is the source of this blog / Digital Garden.
I recorded a video of how I use Obsidian at: How I Use Obsidian</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The application I&rsquo;m writing in at the moment. This is the source of this blog / 





<a
  href="/Digital-Garden/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/Digital-Garden/">Digital Garden</a>.</p>
<p>I recorded a video of how I use Obsidian at: 





<a
  href="/blog/How-I-Use-Obsidian/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/blog/How-I-Use-Obsidian/">How I Use Obsidian</a></p>
<p>How I use statuses in Obsidian: 





<a
  href="/Obsidian-Statuses/"
  rel="noopener" class="internal-link"
  data-src="/Obsidian-Statuses/">Obsidian Statuses</a></p>
<p>For more tips on Obsidian, go check out: 

<a target=“_blank” href="https://github.com/kmaasrud/awesome-obsidian" rel="noopener">https://github.com/kmaasrud/awesome-obsidian</a></p>
<h2 id="tips">Tips</h2>
<ul>
<li>Open the Link under your cursor with CMD+OPT+ENTER</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>VIM</title><link>https://brandonkboswell.com/VIM/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2021 14:13:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://brandonkboswell.com/VIM/</guid><description>Getting started: https://coderwall.com/p/adv71w/basic-vim-commands-for-getting-started
Watching the Thoughtbot training for VIM this dug into f and t for finding a specific character. F will land on it. T will land just prior to it Capital F and Capital T do the same, but in reverse Semicolon repeats Use / for searching.</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Getting started: 

<a target=“_blank” href="https://coderwall.com/p/adv71w/basic-vim-commands-for-getting-started" rel="noopener">https://coderwall.com/p/adv71w/basic-vim-commands-for-getting-started</a></p>
<p>Watching the Thoughtbot training for VIM this dug into
f and t for finding a specific character. F will land on it. T will land just prior to it
Capital F and Capital T do the same, but in reverse
Semicolon repeats
Use / for searching. Use n to go to the next result and shift N to go to the previous


<a target=“_blank” href="https://thoughtbot.com/upcase/videos/onramp-to-vim-motions-and-moving" rel="noopener">https://thoughtbot.com/upcase/videos/onramp-to-vim-motions-and-moving</a></p>
<p>D,A,W to delete the current word including the (delete a word)
If you don&rsquo;t want to lose the space use D,I,W for (delete inner word)</p>
<p>You can do this same thing with paragraphs (contiguous lines) by using the P operator. Ex: &gt;,I,P to indent an entire paragraph</p>
<p>Use CC to empty the current line and begin to replace the contents of that line
Use DD to remove the entire line</p>
<p>CIW to swapping out this word with a completely new one
From this course I learned that I need to use shift on my right hand more. I apparently predominantly manage shift with my right hand, but that makes pressing characters like &quot; difficult as I have to completely leave the home row. They give you a shift on both sides for a reason.</p>
<p>The period key lets you repeat the last command.</p>
<p>The Great Vim Cheat Sheet


<a target=“_blank” href="https://vimsheet.com/" rel="noopener">https://vimsheet.com/</a></p>
<p>

<a target=“_blank” href="https://vimsheet.com/" rel="noopener">https://vimsheet.com/</a></p>
]]></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>